<QUESTS>
	<!-- FISHING - Fishy Joe -->
	<QUEST ID="Q001a">
		<NAME>Menace At The Beach</NAME>
		<START>NPC004</START>
		<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
		<END>NPC004</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Did you hear the rumors? Pandas have said they've seen a shark swimming around at Coconut Beach scaring away the Pandas. A shark in Pandanda Land! I guess crazier things have happened. 
If you feel up for a little adventure, see if you can catch that shark and then bring it to me. 		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>You been brave enough to catch that shark at Coconut Beach? I wouldn't blame you if you're too scared.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Take a look at those teeth! Coconut Beach is safe again! 
Here's a little something for your bravery.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001b">
	    	<NAME>Salmon Run</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, I'm glad you stopped by. I've got a huge order of salmon I need to deliver and I'm a few fish short. You'd be a real life saver if you could bring me 5 salmon by the day's end.
Coconut Beach is the perfect place to fish for the salmon I need.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you had a chance to catch those salmon for me? Head over to Coconut Beach and get fishing, I've got to get that order delivered!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Whew! Just in the nick of time! 
Thanks for your help, here's some coins for the fish.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001c">
	    	<NAME>Old Muddy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Have you heard the legend of Old Muddy? He's the most clever and elusive fish in the Fishing Hole lake. I've spent half my life trying to fish him up.  
I'd give a pretty penny to whoever could catch that old fella.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>One of these days Old Muddy will meet his match!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well I'll be. I never thought I'd see the day when someone would out-smart Old Muddy!
Here's your reward as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001d">
	    	<NAME>Something Fishy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I was out on the lake here the other day fishing when something big grabbed my line. It nearly toppled my boat before yanking my fishing pole right out of my hands! That was my favorite fishing pole too!
Not sure what it was, but it must have been huge! If you can catch whatever it was I'll pay you a handsome reward!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you caught anything in the lake that's big enough to steal my fishing pole?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Woo wee! That's a big one! I'll bet that's the fish that stole my fishing pole!
Here's your reward for catching him!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001e">
	    <NAME>Lobster Dinner</NAME>
	    <START>NPC004</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC004</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>Seems like no matter how many lobsters I catch, Pandas always want more! I'm sold out already today! Could you head over to Coconut Beach and catch me 5 fresh lobsters?
Here, take my lobster trap, that fishing pole won't do you any good.  When you see a lobster swimming around in the water, sneak up on 'em and throw down that trap! </TEXTSTART>
	    <TEXTACTIVE>How you getting along with those lobsters? Not as easy as catching minnows. </TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Ah, look at those beauties! Umm, umm, they look tasty! Here's your reward for a job well done!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001f">
	    	<NAME>Mail Order Mishap</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, glad you're here! I ordered some new fishing gear and it seems the packages got mixed up and were delivered to different parts of Pandanda Land. 
You'd be doing me a huge favor if you could find all my packages and bring them to me. I know one of them ended up at The Big Scoop run by McWiggles. Not sure where the others ended up. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found my packages yet? I'm anxious to try out that new fishing gear.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, you found them. Looks like everything is accounted for. 
Here's some coins to show my appreciation!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001g">
	    	<NAME>Joe's Fish Barbecue</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
How's it going for you buddy? How's fishing these days? I don't know about you, but lots of Pandas have brought me fish and I'm doing a barbecue party later with lots of fish. Sadly, I'm out of coal. Could you please find some for me? You can find it in Pawthorne Forest or on Misty Hill.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found any coal yet? I need you to find me some, it's urgent!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You saved my barbecue fish party! Thanks a lot for the coal, I couldn't find it on my own as I'm preparing lots of stuff. Here's some coins as a thank-you! Also, don't forget to join the feast later!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001h">
	    	<NAME>A Wormy Problem</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Thank god, you're finally here! As you probably know, I usually have lots of bait. But, today! What a day! Everybody's been fishing A LOT. Also, they've been throwing their bait cans in the Fishing Hole, so I'm out of those too! Could you please catch some cans with the rod and get me some worms? Thanks in advance!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I really need those worms and cans. Thanks for trying to help me!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Sweet, you've brought me some cans and bait - you're an amazing friend! Here's a reward for your hard work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001i">
	    	<NAME>Fish for my Daughter</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! Glad you're here. I need you to catch some fish for my daughter - she loves fish! I can't leave the booth right now. So I'll need you to catch 2 Wakin Goldfish and Violet Perches from the lake here and 3 Regal Tang from Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
How's the fishing going so far? Remember - 2 Wakin Goldfish and Violet Perches from the lake here and 3 Regal Tang from Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well done, I'm sure my daughter will love the fish! Here's some coins for your quick work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001j">
	    	<NAME>Shark Danger</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Uh-oh! The big shark is back at Coconut Beach and she's got company this time! We need you to catch them all. Don't be afraid - go ahead.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The sharks are in Coconut Beach. No place for fear, it's all going to go fine.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What a bravery! Thanks for helping us out.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001k">
	    	<NAME>Lost Fruit Snack</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey hey hey! I've heard that a few fellow Pandas have dropped their fruit snack in the Fishing Hole. Could you find it and get it over here? I think it was only apples and oranges.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Grab your fishing rod and catch the apples and oranges from the lake very quick as they can get rotten for very short time span.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
A nice one! Seems like they are still good to be eaten. I'll get them in my fridge and if the Pandas don't come back to look for them, I'll give it to Farmer Dan to make a tasty pie. Mmmm.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001l">
	    	<NAME>Missing Fish Food Cans</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh hi, didn't see you coming. I need your help. There was a truck that was delivering fish food, but seems like it has dropped some. Could you find where they are and bring them to me?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I think that the cans with fish food can be found anywhere. I mean, the truck went around the whole island.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Goodie, you found them all! Thanks a lot. There you go, some coins for your work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001m">
	    	<NAME>Finding Nemo</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Sweet, you're here! Rumors say that a shoal of Clownfish has been spotted near the shore of Abandoned Island. They must have got lost! The Abandoned Island is full of hungry abyssal creatures. This means, if the rumor is true, those clownfish are in a great danger! Can you check if the rumor is real and if so, catch all the Clownfish so that I can let them go safely near Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Hmm, I'm not sure if the rumor is true that there is a shoal of Clownfish there. We have to check!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Seems like it is true, there are Clownfish in the dangerous water. I wonder how those clownfish reached Abandoned Island, it had never happened before as it is barely possible to cross the stormy area near that island... I shall investigate it further and catch the rest. Thanks for your effort, friend, here's a reward for your good deed.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001n">
	    	<NAME>Fish Royalty</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, are you up for a fishing challenge? Well, they say there's plenty of fish in the sea, but the Royal fish are the rarest and the most expensive ones! Therefore, you should be a fishing expert in order to catch these exotic kinds of fish. Remember, they're salt water fish!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The Royal fish are the best. They're salt water fish, keep that in mind!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
I'm impressed by your skills Panda! I must admit, this was indeed a hard task, but you were up for the challenge! I'll put "The Royalties" into an aquarium and give them to Izzy, she will love to take care of them in her shop!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001o">
	    	<NAME>Fishy Potion</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy Panda! As you probably know, I'm in charge of the Fishing Hole and I'm generally a fishing expert. That is why Paige asked me to get some special fish for a very special potion. We've got a lot of going on here so I can't really leave my booth. Could you catch them for me? I'll need 4 Pyramid Butterflyfish and 1 Shark from Coconut Beach, in addition to 3 Violet Perches from Fishing Hole.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm quite busy right now and I can't really catch the fish Paige wants for her potion. Could you get 4 Pyramid Butterflyfish and 1 Shark from Coconut Beach, in addition to 3 Violet Perches from Fishing Hole?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the fish! Those will make a great potion. Tell Joe a hi from me and here you go, some coins to show my thankfulness.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001p">
	    	<NAME>Fishy Bait for Bigger Fish</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! Have you read my fishing book recently? If you have done so, then you most likely know that reusable bait may come in handy when catching fish. I'll be making gold bait - when in water, bigger fish will try eating it but instead, they'll get on the hook. I hope that you'll help me - bring me 3 Small Gold Ores from Harvest Grove and 2 pieces of Cord from urban areas, please.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Reusable bait is in fact quite cheap to make and also quite useful. I'll just need 3 Small Gold Ores from Harvest Grove and 2 pieces of Cord from urban areas and that's it.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Here we go! Some cord here, and the hook and the weight go there... Yup, that's the perfect gold fish bait! Thanks for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001q">
	    	<NAME>Fish Food for the Hole</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings, buddy! Even though the fish may live in the Fishing Hole lake, they need to be fed properly, especially the larger fish and this is why we need to make some food mix. Some of them like eating Seaweed that one can get from Tammy, whereas other prefer salt fish - five Salmons from Coconut Beach would be a feast. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
You'll help me, right mate? You just need some Seaweed from Tammy and five Salmons from Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Yay, the fish will like it! I'm sure they'll thank you as well if they could speak. Here are some coins!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001r">
	    	<NAME>Jellyfish Jam</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day Panda pal! Have you seen those jellyfish around Coconut Beach? I'd like to make some jam with that color. Izzy gave me the recipe but I don't really know how to make it, so, could you give the ingredients to Tammy so that she'll make some for me? Tammy will need 3 Raspberries, 3 Strawberries from Harvest Grove and 1 Large Sugar Beet from The Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Jellyfish Jam sounds tasty. Let's hope it actually tastes well! But for the good taste we'll need 3 Raspberries, 3 Strawberries from Harvest Grove and 1 Large Sugar Beet.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the ingredients, I'll try making this jam because I haven't done it ever before.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001s">
	    	<NAME>Soiling the Hole Lawn</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC014</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! I think Fishing Hole's lawn needs some soiling. There's also high grass and I believe it needs to be cut. Joe has been too busy recently and I think he deserves the help. There are 7 spots that you will notice over time, just observe carefully.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
We do need the Fishing Hole looking in a better and appealing way for the Pandas going there. There are 7 spots that need to be cut and soiled.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks for helping me! I've been too busy to take care of Fishing Hole recently and I'm grateful for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Lisa -->
	<QUEST ID="Q002a">
	    	<NAME>Lost Jewelry!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Help! I've lost my favorite necklace and bracelet! They're my favorite jewelry in the whole world and there's no way I could ever replace them. 
I think I lost my necklace when I was at the beach the other day. But my bracelet probably fell off when I was indoors somewhere.
Could you please go look for them? I'd be really sad if they're gone forever!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm so sad without my jewelry! Have you found anything? 
Be sure to check Coconut Beach for my necklace and The Purple Door, The Big Scoop, and the Book Nook for my bracelet.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You found them! Thank you so much! 
You're my new best friend, just don't tell Sara!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002b">
	    	<NAME>You're Sweet!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh, could you help me? My father gave me a handful of candy earlier but now they're all gone! They must have fallen out of my pocket while I was skipping.
Could you help me look for them? They could be anywhere but I'm sure you could find them if anyone could! You'd be a real friend for helping me!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck finding my candy? I hope someone didn't eat them, that would be awful!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yay, you found them! Thanks a lot! I think I'll eat some now to celebrate.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002c">
	    	<NAME>The Ghost on Misty Hill</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC015</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Have you seen the haunted house on Misty Hill? I have a friend that lives there but he's a little shy around strangers and will only talk to you if you bring him some Ghost Flowers that can be found on Misty Hill. To get to Misty Hill, travel through the back of the woods in Pawthorne Forest.
When you get to the haunted house you'll have to take a secret passage to the Haunted Hallway. That's where you'll find him.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you take some Ghost Flowers to my friend? Make sure to tell him they're from me!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, a visitor! And you brought me Ghost Flowers from Lisa! These are my favorite. 
Please tell her to come and visit me soon. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002d">
	    	<NAME>Late Fees Again?</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Please help me! I have 4 books that are due back to the library tomorrow and I don't know where they are! If I don't return them on time I'll have to pay a late fee!
I remember reading a book at The Den club house in Pawthorne Forest and another at the Book Nook. I'm not sure where the others might be. I'm sure you could find them for me!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you seen my library books? I can't afford any more late fees!
I wish I could remember where I left them all.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Oh great! Thanks a lot! That old Panda at the library won't be mad at me now.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002f">
	    	<NAME>Joe Needs Worms!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Do you know Joe who works over at the Fishing Hole? He asked me to collect a bunch of worms for him to be used as fishing bait but I totally forgot!
Could you help me out and find 5 Small Worms and take them to him? He was going to pay me, so you can keep the coins. You can find worms in Pawthorne Forest, Darby Field, and here in Shady Glen.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find those worms for Fishy Joe yet? I don't want to get in trouble!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, some new fishing bait. Did Lisa give these to you? 
Here's the coins I owe her and tell her thanks for me!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002g">
	    	<NAME>Runaway Dragons</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh please help me! I was pet sitting for some Pandas and while I was out walking the dragons they got off their leashes and escaped! I'll lose my pet sitting job if I cannot find them!
If you happen to find any while you're out walking around please bring them back to me! There are 4 dragons missing all together. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck finding the dragons? If I don't return them to their owners soon, I'll lose my pet sitting job!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh thank you! You really are the nicest Panda! 
Here, you can have these coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002h">
	    	<NAME>A Message from Abandoned Island</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Heya! How's your day going so far? I've been told that somebody saw a message bottle in Coconut Beach for from the other side of Pandanda Land - Abandoned Island. Could you find it and bring it to me? I wonder what's it about, Abandoned Island is quite a scary area...
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The message bottle may be deep in the water, so look carefully for it. I'm still trying to figure out who is the sender...
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
This message is from my friend, Jasper! He's on a ghost holiday on the Abandoned Island. Thanks for bringing me the message!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002i">
	    	<NAME>Fresh Smoothie Ingredients</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What a nice day on Pandanda Land! It's sunny and warm, mmm... and I'm really thirsty! A good smoothie in such a hot day is always good. But, I'll need some ingredients to make it. Could you bring me please a quart of milk from Farmer Dan, 2 red apples, 2 green apples and 3 peaches? Thanks in advance!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Oh, it's really hot. I'm waiting for you to get me the ingredients for a good smoothie, I know you're a good Panda and you will help me out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
This tastes good! Here's a smoothie for you as well, try it out and here's some coins to get an ice cream from my dad, we really need to get refreshed once in a while.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002j">
	    	<NAME>Apples for Apple Feast</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Today, I gotta host an apple feast in my treehouse. But, I need somebody to help me out with collecting the apples. I'll be here preparing the pastry while you're collecting apples from The Orchard. I'll need 3 green apples, 3 red apples and 3 small apples.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Are there apples in The Orchard? I heard that some of them have already been collected, so I suggest you to hurry up.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Sweet, those apples will be enough for my feast. Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002k">
	    	<NAME>A Herbarium</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! What a beautiful day it is, isn't it? The birds are singing, the flowers are blooming, the leaves are falling off the trees... I'd like to make a herbarium and I'll need some leaves. Could you collect some from The Orchard, Pawthorne Forest and Treehouse Lobby? Make sure they've got different colors so that the herbarium will become more interesting.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I guess I'll need some more leaves than what you have collected. Look for some in The Orchard, Pawthorne Forest or Treehouse Lobby.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
These leaves look colorful. They'll make a great herbarium! Thanks for your help, here's something for you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002l">
	    	<NAME>Bracelets for my BFFs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! How's your day going, buddy? You know, Friendship Festival isn't the only time when we show our appreciation to our best friends. So, I'd like to give out some bracelets to all my best friends! Here's one for you and could you please give the rest to Farmer Dan, Farmer Ned, Paige, Lily, Jim and Mr. Elmhurst? Thanks in advance!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Thanks for promising to help me out with giving those bracelets to my best friends! I see you still have some, don't hurry, you can give them whenever you can.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yey, thanks for giving them out! Here's some coins, bestie.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002m">
	    <NAME>A Forbidden Love</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Oh, you're here! My dear Jasper is in trouble! The ghosts on Misty Hill discovered our secret love, and for them, it is unacceptable for a ghost to love a flesh and bone Panda. Now there is a rebellion after Jasper, and only you can stop them! Please save my love!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Those angry ghosts wouldn't like me to love Jasper. Please, help me out!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks, without you, those ghosts would have found Jasper in his secret hideout. Here is a reward for your kindness and bravery. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002n">
	    <NAME>Parlour Spies</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! I know I can trust you Panda... you know, Jasper and I, we are meeting in secret in The Parlour. I use the secret passage from Book Nook so that the other ghosts won't notice me coming in. However, Jasper suspects that they have set up some eyes in order to spy on us. That cannot happen! Can you go to The Parlour and see if this is true?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You may have to be patient, those eyes for sure are hidden well.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Jasper was right! There's a thing I don't understand, though - why they can't accept that Jasper and I are in love? They're trying their best to tear our relationship apart, but that wouldn't work. Thank you, Panda, for helping me once again with those angry ghosts.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002o">
	    <NAME>Juggling Tricks</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Panda, Panda, come here, I wanna show you a trick! I'm going to juggle with these coconuts, will you watch? I'm practising for a talent show! *drops the coconuts* Oh, no! They cracked and those were the last ones Tammy had! Can you find me some more, otherwise I wouldn't be able to participate in the talent show!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Thanks for trying to find coconuts for me!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thank you so much, the next time you see me, I will be an expert juggler, I promise! I have a something little for you because you were so generous - take it!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002p">
	    <NAME>Gem Necklace</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC007</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there! I really need a new necklace. However, I need some gems and I can't really create it myself. Could you collect some red Rubies from Darby Field and some Cord from the urban areas and take it to Jim?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You can always find red Rubies in Darby Field. Jim will definitely make a beautiful one.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Okay, these Rubies are perfect. Here you go - give Lisa the necklace.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002q">
	    <NAME>Gem Necklace</NAME>
	    <START>NPC007</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Okay, these Rubies are perfect. Here you go - give Lisa the necklace.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Okay, these Rubies are perfect. Here you go - give Lisa the necklace.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Oh thank you very much! Here are some coins! Please also tell Jim thanks from me.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002r">
	    <NAME>Egg-y Help</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day buddy! I'm a hurry right now so I'll be very grateful if you can help. My dad asked me for some ingredients for a cake and I can't really get them right now. He'll be making a special one, so he'll need 2 Brown Eggs, 2 White Eggs and 2 Green Eggs from Farmer Ned's Barn. Oh, and some milk from Farmer Dan.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Oh my, thank you so much for helping me! You're definitely doing some good job. I can't really leave Shady Glen right now, I need to watch out for dangerous animals.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Lisa sent you? Oh my poor daughter, she must be very busy. Big thanks for the ingredients!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002s">
	    <NAME>Shady Planting</NAME>
	    <START>NPC024</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! My friend Lisa asked me for some seeds to plant in Shady Glen. Since I'm not able to plant them myself because I need to take care of the horses, could you do that for me and Lisa?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Lisa will surely like these daffodils in Shady Glen!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
These daffodils give a sunnier look to Shady Glen and it's no longer that shady! You're a very good gardener - here is a payment for your hard work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002t">
	    <NAME>Feeding Fish</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello! Do you like fish? I do a lot! I love the ones in Fishing Hole and I'd like to help Joe feeding them. Can you do that for me so that the nice little cute fish will get an extra treat?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Yay, the cute little fish in Fishing Hole are getting an extra treat!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thank you very much for helping! Joe also is grateful. Take those coins!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002u">
	    <NAME>Izzy's Pets</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC012</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Ey bud! Izzy is very sad. She has lost all her pets and I really want to cheer her up. We shall find her pets - a dragon, a bunny and two Violet Perches. The dragon can be literally everywhere, the bunnies are shy so it's hiding in the grass somewhere - wait for the grass to start shaking - and you can fish Violet Perches from Fishing Hole.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Izzy is really sad and we need to find her lost pets.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Oh my dragon! Oh my bunny! Oh my Perches! Thank you, thank you so much, Panda! You are a true friend!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- McWiggles -->
	<QUEST ID="Q003a">
	    	<NAME>Strawberry Cream Swirl</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, so glad you're here! I'm running low on ingredients for my famous Strawberry Cream Swirl. It's my best seller, you know.
Let's see... I'll need a Quart of Cream, 1 Large Sugar Beet from the Orchard, and 3 Large Strawberries. Farmer Dan will have the cream and Harvest Grove is the best place to pick strawberries. Hurry along now.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Have you had a chance to gather those ingredients for me? Pandas are clamoring for my strawberry ice cream!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Excellent, exactly what I needed! These strawberries look mighty fresh!
Here, take some coins for your trouble.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003b">
	    	<NAME>Sweet and Sour</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I was supposed to get some items for McWiggles who works at The Big Scoop, but I completely forgot. Something about Lemon ice cream...
I think he needed a Quart of Cream, a Large Sugar Beet, and some Large Lemons. Would you collect those items and take them to him for me? Farmer Dan should have the cream for sale and you can get sugar beets from the Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you get the items for McWiggles? Don't tell him I forgot about it!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, just in time. I was almost out of my lemon ice cream! 
I was beginning to think Paige forgot about me.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003c">
	    	<NAME>A New Taste Sensation</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, you're just in time to help me with my latest ice cream creation! It's got a little bit of cinnamon, a touch of spice root, and ... well, the rest is my little secret. Although, I do need a few more ingredients if you have the time. 
If you could bring me a Quart of Cream, 2 Large Sugar Beets from the Orchard, and 2 Fresh Honey Combs from Pawthorne Forest, I'd be forever grateful! Farmer Dan will sell you the cream.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How are you coming along with those ingredients? I know this will be my greatest creation yet!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Splendid! These look nice and fresh! You might have a future in culinary arts. 
Here's some compensation for your effort.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003d">
	    	<NAME>Fresh from the Farm</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC014</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! Feel like makin' a delivery for me? McWiggles, who runs The Big Scoop, asked me to get a few supplies for him but I got busy with other things.
Now where did I put that list? Ah, here we are, he needs a Quart of Cream, a Large Sugar Beet, and 3 Sweet Cherries. I reckon you can find the cherries and sugar beet at the Orchard easy enough, then talk to Farmer Dan for the cream. Best be runnin' off now, don't want to keep McWiggles waiting.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
You get those supplies for McWiggles yet? I know he was in a hurry to get them.
You'll find him in The Big Scoop ice cream parlor when you're done. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, the supplies I needed from Farmer Ned! Looks like everything is here, thanks.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003e">
	    	<NAME>The Sugar Toothed Tailor</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC008</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC008</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! I was getting some ice cream from McWiggles the other day and heard him say he is trying to come up with new recipes for ice cream flavors. 
I bet if you took him a some Fresh Honey Comb, a few Large Sugar Beets, and a couple Large Blueberries, he could make something really tasty. You'll find the honey comb in Pawthorne Forest, sugar beets in the Orchard, and head over to Harvest Grove for the blueberries.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get those ingredients for McWiggles yet?
Once you have them you'll probably find him in The Big Scoop ice cream parlor.
I can't wait to see what new flavors he comes up with.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, more flavors for my ice cream experiments! 
Here, have some coins for your kindness.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003f">
	    	<NAME>Berrylicious</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Nice to see you again! I've heard there are delicious looking Red Raspberries growing over in Harvest Grove. I think they would make an excellent addition to my ice cream selection, don't you?
Would you mind picking some Red Raspberries and bringing them to me? I'll gladly pay you for you time. I could also use a Large Sugar Beet from the Orchard and a Quart of Cream from Farmer Dan if it's no trouble.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find the Red Raspberries over at Harvest Grove? I can't wait to whip up some a new ice cream flavor.
Don't forget the cream and sugar beet.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, thank you! I'll start work on my raspberry ice cream first thing tomorrow. 
Here's your payment. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<QUEST ID="Q003g">
	    	<NAME>A Cake for a Cupcake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! It's my cupcake Lisa's birthday and I really want to get her the cake she loves - a Rhubarb Cake. Sadly though, I don't remember the recipe. I wrote in this letter to Paige some plans for Lisa's birthday tonight, so bring it to her and ask for the recipe, please. I can't do it because I can't leave The Big Scoop right now.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you visited Paige yet? Please give her the letter I gave you and don't forget to ask for the Rhubarb Cake recipe.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Howdy! How's it been going for you recently? Oh, I see you have a letter for me - wow, it's the plans for Lisa's Birthday Party. Do you want the recipe for her favorite cake?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003h">
	    	<NAME>A Cake for a Cupcake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Sweet! So here you go - 2 rhubarb leaves, 1 large sugar beet, a quart of cream from Farmer Dan, 3 strawberries, 3 blueberries, 2 brown eggs. I know it's a lot but the cake is going to be EXTREMELY HUGE!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I need you to find all those ingredients in order to get the cake ready. They are 2 rhubarb leaves, 1 large sugar beet, a quart of cream from Farmer Dan, 3 strawberries, 3 blueberries, 2 brown eggs. I know it's a lot but the cake is going to be EXTREMELY HUGE!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
I'm going to get the cake ready now. Come back later and I'll give it to you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003i">
	    	<NAME>A Cake for a Cupcake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! The cake for Lisa's Birthday Party is ready, would you like to take it to William McWiggles in The Big Scoop.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Hurry up, take the cake to The Big Scoop, Lisa's Birthday Party is starting soon.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, thank you very much, you really saved the day! The cake is going to wait for Lisa over here at The Big Scoop.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003j">
	    	<NAME>A Cake for a Cupcake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh, I totally forgot about this one! I've got an invitation for her, but I lost it! Could you please find it and bring it to her? I think I dropped it when I visited Fishy Joe yesterday, or it was when visiting Fitch? It could have also happened when I was at The Orchard to collect some apples, and then when I brought it to Mr. Elmhurst's cart.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Oh, I totally forgot about this one! I've got an invitation for her, but I lost it! Could you please find it and bring it to her? I think I dropped it when I visited Fishy Joe yesterday, or it was when visiting Fitch? It could have also happened when I was at The Orchard to collect some apples, and then when I brought it to Mr. Elmhurst's cart. Oh, and don't tell her that I wrote it!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, a surprise party for another citizen of Pandanda Land? I'll surely go, I'm also excited to get an invitation for my surprise as well! Somebody probably sent you, so I guess I have to give the prize. Here you go.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003k">
	    	<NAME>Ice Cream Shortage</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! I've been running short on ice cream ingredients. I need somebody to help me out with collecting 3 blueberries, 2 raspberries - from Harvest Grove and 2 quarts of cream from Farmer Dan. Could you help me?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Raspberries and blueberries can be usually found in Harvest Grove, whereas Farmer Dan is in Darby Field - you can get the quarts of cream.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
There we go, thanks a lot! Here's some coins.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003l">
	    	<NAME>Redecorating The Big Scoop</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello there! How's your day going so far? Anything interesting? Today, I decided to redecorate The Big Scoop. I ordered some decorations but seems like it all got messed up and the order is late already. I need you to wait for the crates to appear after they get delivered. You need to wait here in The Big Scoop, The Den, Book Nook and Bear Hollow. I'll also need some glue which is inside some building.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found all the crates and the glue yet?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Phew, I thought that they'll never be delivered. Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003m">
	    	<NAME>Fish for an Aquarium</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! What a beautiful day! It's perfect for fishing! Speaking of fishing, I would like to ask you if you could catch some fish for The Big Scoop's upcoming aquarium. I'll need 2 Calico Goldfish, 3 Black Angelfish from Fishing Hole and 1 Orange Clownfish from Coconut Beach. I'll ask other citizens to bring me some, too. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Are there any clownfish left at Coconut Beach? I heard that they were a nearly rare catch.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
These fishes look brilliant! They're really colorful. Your help is appreciated!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003n">
	    	<NAME>Vegetable Ice Cream</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I've decided to experiment further and present to my customers a new kind of ice cream... vegetable ice cream! Might sound weird, but I want to see if there are any pandas who'll buy it. So, here's the recipe - 1 Sugar Beet from the Orchard to give it a somewhat sweet taste, 2 Purple Carrots, 1 Cabbage and 2 Rhubarbs. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you collected all the vegetables yet? I'm not really sure if people will like carrots with sugar, but I guess they'd like to try it out anyway.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
I can start experimenting now! Here's your coins.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003o">
	    	<NAME>Rare Eggs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! I heard that Farmer Ned's white chicken have been giving... colorfil eggs! It is said that there are green, blue and white eggs. Could you collect 2 of each kind and bring them to Jim later so he can say what's going on for sure? Thanks! 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The strange rare eggs are in Farmer Ned's Barn and they are given by his white chicken, isn't it?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, just as McWiggles told me - they are in different colors. Thanks for bringing them to me, here are some coins for the time you've devoted.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003p">
	    	<NAME>Frosty Trouble</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! After the recent power outage, my refrigerators aren't working properly. The clients are dissatisfied because their ice cream melts way too quickly. I have to repair the refrigerators, but I'll need some help. Can you buy a screwdriver from Jim, find 5 iron strings from the big squares and two moonstones from Pawthorne Forest? Thanks in advance!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Can you buy a screwdriver from Jim, find 5 iron strings from the big squares and two moonstones from Pawthorne Forest? I can't leave my shop because I've got a lot of clients today.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
A few tweaks and here we go - all the refrigerators are working perfectly again! I think that you have just saved my business, I don't know how to thank you! I'll try, though: here are some coins.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003q">
	    	<NAME>When Spiders Attack</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Here's your ice cream Panda! Wait, what's this on it? A spider? Oh my! How it is possible? I always clean my place! THEY ARE EVERYWHERE! Panda, please, I need your help, we need to catch those spiders before anyone else comes in here, will you give me a hand?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'll definitely need your help with those spiders. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
I think we caught every spider, thanks! Now I'll let them go in Pawthorne Forest, where they are supposed to be.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003r">
	    	<NAME>A Soup Cure</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day, nice to see you again! My daughter Lisa isn't feeling very well. She's got a cold perhaps or it's the flu. I'll be making her a soup after I'm done here for today but I'll need some products. May you bring me some spices from Farmer Ned, a few potatoes and two carrots?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I hope that my soup will help Lisa. I mean, I haven't cooked one in ages but I hope I've still got my skills. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the ingredients! I've got a couple more hours here at work but I'll do my best to have it ready after that.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003s">
	    	<NAME>Coconut Ice</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I'll be making my very special ice cream with coconut taste. I can give you some after you help me out. Could you bring me 5 Coconuts, 1 Quart of Cream and 1 Large Sugar Beet?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The Coconut Ice flavor is always refreshing, no matter the season.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
These are enough! I'll hand you a cone when I get enough of it ready.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003t">
	    	<NAME>Bunnies for Dan</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Good day, my friend! You probably know who Farmer Dan is. Yeah, the guy with the bunnies who also offers the best milk for my icecream. I've decided that I'd like to return the favor and help him out with finding some of his lost bunnies. Since I'm pretty busy experimenting here with new flavors and I need to visit Lisa later, could you help me out with finding some of those bunnies? All I know about them is that they're gray and they're not in the urban areas of our Land. Watch out for the grass shaking - that may be a clear sign of those bunnies hiding behind a patch!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Those gray bunnies may be hiding very well. You need to look carefully around rural areas. Oh, and watch out - they are hiding behind patches of grass and you should notice when some grass is shaking.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for helping me with finding those bunnies! Padlocks, iron strings, nothing can stop these fluffy baddies, haha.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003u">
	    	<NAME>Cone Decorations</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! What a sunny weather it is today, Panda! I decided to make my icecream cones look fresher than ever and so today I'll be serving them with a few feathers attached. I'll be glad if you can find 5 Brown Feathers, 5 Colorful Feathers and 5 Yellow Feathers. They can be found literally everywhere outside The Big Scoop.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Attaching Colorful Feathers to the cone in my opinion will make it look very fresh and tropical. You can find some of these outside The Big Scoop.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Fresh colors is what those feathers have! Here are some coins for your good job.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003v">
	    	<NAME>Let's do the Watering</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey Panda! Recently, I've got a lot into ecology and actually caring for the nature - thanks to Steve. So I want really bad to do my good deed of the day today but there are tons of orders. I'd like to ask you if you could water the trees in The Orchard on the spots marked with crosses, as well as the soil in Harvest Grove - that would be very kind of yours. Oh, and you can also have your good deed of the day!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Whereas most of us pick fruits from the trees in The Orchard, it's not only Steve and Tammy's responsibility to take care of them. We should too.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for watering the plants! Do you feel any good from doing a good deed?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Tammy Tomato -->
	<QUEST ID="Q004a">
	    	<NAME>A Green Thumb</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi, would you like to help me with some gardening? I have several gardens set up at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove that are ready for planting.
Take these flower seeds and plant them in each of the gardens. Make sure you get them all! Come back and see me when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you plant all the flower seeds at my gardens? They will be so pretty!
You can find the gardens set up at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.
 		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks! You've been a great help. 
I can't wait for the flowers bloom!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004b">
	    	<NAME>The Thirsty Flowers</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Would you like to help me out with my flowers? They're starting to droop and need watering. I'd do it myself but don't have time to get to them today. 
Take this watering can and visit my flowers in the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove. Be sure to bring my watering can back when you're done!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Make sure you water all the flowers really well. I'm sure they are thirsty!
You can find the drooping flowers at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Thanks for your help! I'll go by later to see how they look.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004c">
	    	<NAME>A Bouquet for Tammy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Have you seen my flower gardens? They are in full bloom right now and so beautiful! Would you be so kind as to pick some flowers from each of my gardens and bring them to me?
You'll find the flowers in the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Be careful when picking the flowers, they can be very delicate.
You can find the flowers blooming at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>These are beautiful! Thank you for your help!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004d">
	    	<NAME>Making Compost</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I've found a great way to fertilize my garden soil by adding organic compost. I make my own compost but I could use help getting a few more materials like leaves, grass clippings, and old newspapers to mix in.
You can find Grass Clippings in Darby Field, Leaves in Pawthorne Forest, and Newspapers in one of the towns. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you gather the compost materials I need for my organic compost? I'll shred them up and add start a new compost bin.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Great! Thanks for your help, these will do wonderfully.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004e">
	    	<NAME>Enriching the Soil</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi, I've got some organic compost that needs to be added to my gardens. Would you mind helping me out, if you're not too busy?
All you need to do is visit my gardens at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove and add the compost to the Garden Soil. Be sure to bring back the wheelbarrow once you've finished.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you add the compost to all of the gardens? The compost needs to be added before I can plant any more flowers.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Thanks! I'm sure the enriched soil will really help my flowers!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004f">
	    	<NAME>A Healthy Snack for Friends</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Heya, I decided to organize a picnic for my friends with only organic food - fruits. I'll need 2 red apples, some cherries, 2 oranges and 3 peaches. Could you get this all for me? You can find all the fruits in The Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm pretty sure it's the season for all the fruits I asked you for, so go ahead. Oh, don't forget - you're also invited to my picnic!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>These fruits are really fresh, thanks! It seems like the picnic will be awesome. Come and join us later!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004g">
	    	<NAME>Vegetable Soup</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! What's healthier to eat for lunch than a vegetable soup? Energy and healthy food combined! So, I'll need an onion, some cabbage, some potatoes and some carrots. Could you help me out? I'll give you a portion of it as well as some coins later.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
All the vegetables can be found in Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Mm, these smell nice! Come see me later for a portion. Here's your coins now.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004h">
	    	<NAME>Fish and Radishes Soup</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day! It's me again with my soup experiments. I'll be making today some soup with fish and radishes. I'll need 2 smelts and 3 radishes. Would you find some time to get some for me?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Are you having tough times finding the ingredients? I'm pretty sure that there is smelt in the Fishing Hole lake and there are surely radishes in Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Sweet, thanks for the ingredients! You're always welcome to stop by and have a healthy soup.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004i">
	    	<NAME>Cake for Steve's Birthday</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! It's Tammy's brother Steve birthday soon and we really need a cake for him. She asked me for the tasty berry cake recipe. You'll have to bring her the ingredients later. Keep any coins she gives you. So, you'll need 5 raspberries, 5 blackberries, 2 eggs and 2 sugar beets. Raspberries can be found at Harvest Grove, eggs - in Farmer Ned's Barn and sugar beets in The Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
How's the berry collection going? Any luck finding raspberries and blackberries?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Thanks for the ingredients, now I'm ready to start preparing Steve's cake. Bring these coins to McWiggles.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004j">
	    	<NAME>Fortune Cookies for my Friends</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello fellow Panda pal! Since I love all my friends, I decided to give them fortune cookies. Here's a bunch of them to give to Paige, Lily, Mr. Elmhurst, Steve, Jim, Izzy, Joe, William McWiggles and Lisa McWiggles. Also, don't forget to visit me and remind me for your fortune cookie after you gave the rest to my friends, you're also special!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Please, give a cookie to Paige, Lily, Mr. Elmhurst, Steve, Jim, Izzy, Joe, William McWiggles and Lisa McWiggles. Oh, and make sure you remind me for your cookie!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>You're an amazing friend just like my other friends are! Thanks for everything!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004k">
	    	<NAME>Coconut Madness</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Since the grand opening of Community Center, my special fruit cocktails have become really famous! Im feeling creative, so Ill try a new recipe: the Coconut Madness. Listen closely and learn what the secret ingredients are ...*whispers* Four coconuts, A Quarter of Cream and a Large Sugar Beet. Can you bring those to me? Don't tell anyone my recipe or why you're looking for these ingredients!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Don't forget: don't tell my secret recipe to anyone!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Now Ill blend the ingredients... give it a try! I knew it, I found the perfect mix! Thanks for your help and keeping my recipe a secret.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004l">
	    	<NAME>Growing Tomatoes</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! I know you're a really good green thumb and you like planting. As you probably know, my favorite vegetable are tomatoes and we can plant together some later. However, we'll need seeds - and in order to get some seeds, we'll need a couple tomatoes so that we can extract them. Tomatoes grow in Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Mmmm, those tasty red tomatoes in Harvest Grove! They'll definitely give a good harvest after we plant their seeds.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>And we've got them! Thanks for the help, talk to me in a few weeks if you want to plant the seeds with me.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004m">
	    	<NAME>Tomatoes and Cucumbers</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day! What a weather! I'd really love a nice fresh salad. But what ingredients should we choose? Hmm... Let's have something from the Bulgarian cuisine. A tomatoes and cucumbers salad, mmm, it sounds tasty! We'll need a few tomatoes and a few cucumbers from Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I really need something refreshing, the tomato and cucumber salad is the best in this case.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Thanks for the vegetables! Would you like to stop by for a salad?</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004n">
	    	<NAME>Regular Carrot Supply</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! Farmer Dan asked me for the regular carrot supply but I'm really busy here and I can't really do it. He said it's urgent. Could you collect 4 Orange Carrots, 4 Yellow Carrots and 4 Purple Carrots?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Those carrots are really urgent, I really hope that you'll bring them soon.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Thanks for helping me out! Could you deliver them to Farmer Dan?</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004o">
	    	<NAME>Regular Carrot Supply</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Thanks for helping me out! Could you deliver them to Farmer Dan?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Thanks for helping me out! Could you deliver them to Farmer Dan?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Oh wow, so that's my regular carrot supply. Here is your payment. Are you the new supplier?</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004p">
	    	<NAME>Cleaning Up for Steve</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there fellow buddy! Have you noticed Pandas throwing fruit here and there? I saw quite a few today and I didn't like that - it takes a lot of time and effort to grow them! Also, they get rotten and make the ground a complete mess. My friend Steve can't clean that many so I want to ask you if you can join me and help me clean up for him.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Steve really needs help. He'll appreciate it a lot!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Wait, where did the rotten fruits go? Oh, you and Tammy have cleaned it for me? Oh my god, thank you so much, you've saved me a lot of time!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004q">
	    	<NAME>Corn Booth</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What a day, pal! I decided that I really want to have some boiled corn with salt but I don't really have any of these. Oh, also an idea crossed my mind - let's also give some corn to Pandas for free, that's a delight! Will you help me out by bringing me 5 Corn Cobs from Harvest Grove and some Salt from Fishy Joe?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Fishy Joe has the best salt on mPandanda Land. It'll make the corn cobs delicious!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Alright let's boil these and start giving them around. Yum!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004r">
	    	<NAME>Go Vegan</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Have you heard about being a vegan? Sounds interesting and I'd like to try! I'll start off by making vegan sandwiches for my friends and I. We're going to have a vegan picnic! I'll be preparing the potato bread by myself so I'll need some flour and potatoes as well as some onion and rhubarb. I'll be glad if you can help me with getting these ingredients.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The vegan sandwiches are going to taste really well, Maggie gave me the recipe.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Okay, we're good to go! I'll make the sandwiches and make sure to be here at 3 because we'll be going on the picnic together.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<!-- Steve McClean -->
	<QUEST ID="Q005a">
	    	<NAME>Soiled Again</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What a fine day we're having! If you're not too busy, or planning to take a nap, perhaps you could help me with my environmental studies of Pandanda Land.
I've placed yellow flags in several locations around Pandanda where I'd like you to collect soil samples. Once you have them all bring them back here. Do you think you could manage that? 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I need those soil samples so I can perform my environmental tests.
Look for the yellow flags like the ones in Darby Field and Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, thank you! These will do nicely. 
Here's some coins for your assistance.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005b">
	    	<NAME>It's Always Sunny in Pandanda</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Nice weather we're having today! I like to keep track of weather patterns across Pandanda, a little hobby of mine. I could use a little help if you've got the time.
I've marked out several locations around Pandanda where I'd like you to take weather readings. Take this weather device with you and place it down on the marked spots like the one in West Market Street.  Bring it back once you've finished, it's the only weather device I have! Oh, and I also need you to get a water sample from Fishing Hole.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you take those weather readings yet? You'll find one of the lighted green X markings in West Market Street to get you started.
Please be careful with my weather device, it's expensive!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Done already? I'll process the weather data when I get back to my tree house. 
Thanks again!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005c">
	    	<NAME>Make Sure it's Pure</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
All this recycling got me thinking of how to reduce plastic bottles, so I've been working on my own water purifier. But I need more water samples to test it out. You look like you could use some work, what do you say?
Head over to the Fishing Hole and Coconut Beach and bring me back 2 water samples from each location. You'll see a yellow bobber where to take the samples from. Make sure you keep them separated! 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>My water purifier might just put an end to all these plastic bottles.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Ah, there you are. And you got the water samples, great! 
I'll let you know when my purifier is up and running.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005d">
	    	<NAME>Sounds of Serenity</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Is there anything more peaceful than the sounds of the ocean? I'm putting together a "Serene Sounds of Pandanda" cd to help me relax after a hard day. Think you could help me collect the sound samples?
I've marked out some spots around Pandanda that provide the perfect tranquil sounds I'm looking for. All you have to do is take this recorder and place it on the marked spots in each location, then bring it back when you're finished.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Hey, how are the sound recordings coming along? 
The best spots to record are Coconut Beach, The Fishing Hole, Shady Glen, Pawthorne Forest, and Harvest Grove. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, wonderful you're back. I'll take a listen to these this evening. 
Have a few coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005e">
	    	<NAME>Cleaning Up the Lake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I heard some Pandas were fishing over at the Fishing Hole and fished up some old junk out of the lake! We all gotta do our part to keep Pandanda clean. Feel like helping out?
Head over to the Fishing Hole and fish up 3 pieces of junk out of the lake. Bring em back and I'll make sure they get disposed of properly. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to fish up any junk from the lake? I'm sure the fish will appreciate it too!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Look at this old junk. Well, you've done your part and the lake is clean once again. 
Here's some coins for you help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005f">
	    	<NAME>Even More Trash in the Lake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I heard some Pandas were fishing over at the Fishing Hole and fished up even more junk! I don't like Pandas that get the water dirty. I need you to get all the new trash out of the lake.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to fish up any junk from the lake? I'm sure the fish will appreciate it too!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, even more soda cans and plastic bottles! Accept these coins as a thank-you for your good deed.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005g">
	    	<NAME>Recycling Paper</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What a nice day to recycle paper! Recycling is good for the environment, so we'll need to collect some stuff like old books and newspapers. I heard that there was an old copy of The Princess and The Panda as well as an old copy of Paige's Book in Book Nook, the rest ended up somewhere indoors.
I was also told that there were few old newspaper copies outdoors, collect them all as well.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found all the paper around the island yet?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Sweet, that's a lot of paper. I also collected some and together we've saved the environment again!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005h">
	    	<NAME>Collecting Trash</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I've seen lots of trash around recently and I've been doing my best but it's simply impossible to collect it all. I saw a lot of plastic bottles and old cans so I suggest you to collect 10 of each.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I know it's a lot of plastic bottles and soda cans but I'm sure you'll do great!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well done! Here's some coins for your hard work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005i">
	    	<NAME>Berries and Radishes</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What a beaufitul day! Berries and radishes are awesome fruits and vegetables to cook. I heard that McWiggles has berry ice cream flavors as well as vegetable ice cream flavor. I need you to collect some raspberries, blackberries and radishes. Head over to Harvest Grove, you'll find them all there.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The day is nice and I'm pretty sure that there are some berries and radishes at Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
These will surely help me with making more ice cream, I've recently been short on berries for my fruit ice cream flavors as well as radishes for the vegetable ice cream.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005j">
	    	<NAME>Organic Paint</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
It's awesome that we managed to recycle a lot! Pandas have been giving lots of organic stuff recently and I was able to make some organic paint. Could you give it to McWiggles, Lisa, Paige, Lily, Joe, Tammy, Jim, Mr. Elmhurst, Farmer Ned, Farmer Dan, Fitch, Izzy and Maggie? Make sure to come back for some paint for you too after you give it to the rest.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Don't hurry, the organic paint won't get bad quick. Give it please to McWiggles, Lisa, Paige, Lily, Joe, Tammy, Jim, Mr. Elmhurst, Farmer Ned, Farmer Dan, Fitch, Izzy and Maggie and don't forget to visit me after that for your paint.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for giving all the paint out! It's really good to use organic paint rather than one which damages the environment.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005k">
	    	<NAME>Lost Snowman Decorations</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! As you may know, there were snowmen around up until some point of time and seems like some of their decorations were lost. One Panda told me that there's a top hat and a scarf indoors in two different locations. Could you find them and bring them to me? This way we'll keep the buildings clean and we may use them again next winter.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I heard that the scarf was in Book Nook. Where did the top hat go though?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Good job, you found them. I'll now keep them here for the next snowmen makers.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005l">
	    	<NAME>A Frightening Night</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! I'm glad you arrived. You won't believe this: I was doing my regular weather check-up, when my weather device suddenly caught a weird interference from Abandoned Island at 3am this morning! After that... the recording wasn't even finished, it just had a blank space in the end, as if the device got shut down. I think that there's an encrypted message hidden in this recording. Could you take it to Jim and ask him what's up with all this?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I really hope that Jim can understand what happened in the end of that recording.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Quite interesting, I have to agree with Steve, the end of the recording is way too coordinated to be pure gibberish. It looks like a sinusoid... a repetitive wave movement. I will try to figure it all out, but I burnt my antennas last night with some experiments... if you bring me 5 iron strings I may be able to fix them and then I'll try understanding what does this all mean.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005m">
	    	<NAME>A Frightening Night</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Quite interesting, I have to agree with Steve, the end of the recording is way too coordinated to be pure gibberish. It looks like a sinusoid... a repetitive wave movement. I will try to figure it all out, but I burnt my antennas last night with some experiments... if you bring me 5 iron strings I may be able to fix them and then I'll try understanding what does this all mean.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
You can find old iron strings in all the squares nearby. I'll need them to fix my antennas.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Those seem perfect! Some last adjustments and... I think it will work now! *clicks and key tapping* Done!... *high pitch noise* Arrrgh, THIS SOUND IS TERRIBLE, cover your ears! *BZZZZKT!*
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005n">
	    	<NAME>A Frightening Night</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
That amount of energy... I still cant believe it! I hope that the power generators didnt fry, just like my computer! The signal came from the Abandoned Island, but I dont get it, how was a simple recording capable of consuming such amount of power? We must check out the generat... AAAAARGH A GHOST, RIGHT BEHIND YOU! 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
That amount of energy... I still cant believe it! I hope that the power generators didnt fry, just like my computer! The signal came from the Abandoned Island, but I dont get it, how was a simple recording capable of consuming such amount of power? We must check out the generat... AAAAARGH A GHOST, RIGHT BEHIND YOU! 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks, you saved mPandanda... literally! Without your bravery, the streets would now be haunted by ghosts. I still dont get how these strange things are happening... but it all seems related to Abandoned Island in some way. This mystery is far from solved...
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005o">
	    	<NAME>Cleaning up Leaves</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! It's also good to clean up the non-urban areas, you know. It's not very nice to walk through piles of leaves in the forest and I think you could agree with me. I'd like to ask you to clean up all piles of leaves you can find in Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Even though it's a forest, you can't walk through piles of leaves.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yay, you did it, thanks! I'll recycle the leaves and probably make organic compost, here's something for your job well done.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005p">
	    	<NAME>Clipping Grass</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ey there buddy! Have you seen randomly appearing patches of grass in the pavement holes? Could you clip all the grass in the urban areas so that the streets look more clean?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Clipping the grass from the pavement makes the streets look cleaner.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Good job! Now our village has a better outlook.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005q">
	    	<NAME>Salt Water in Fresh Water</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Some Pandas have told me that they have caught some aquarium salt water fish in the Fishing Hole. I was astonished so I decided to check out myself and it turned out to be true! Could you help me and Joe with catching all the Salt Water Fish that is there?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Salt Water Fish has nothing to do in Fishing Hole. We need to move them back to Fishing Hole!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for catching all the Salt Water Fish here in the lake! I'll move them to Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005r">
	    	<NAME>Dirty Pavement</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! Have you seen some lumps of dirt in West Market Street and in Bear Hollow? I've noticed them and I thought that they'd be useful for soiling the ground in order to make it more fertile. Could you clean them all up and bring me those later?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
It's not just me who has noticed the lumps of dirt. They have to be cleaned up as soon as possible.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh yay, thanks! Those lumps will make the soil very fertile. Well done!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005s">
	    	<NAME>Salty Seaweed</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day pal! Do you like seaweed? And a seaweed pizza? What about some sea salt on the pizza as well? I love sea salt pizza with garlic, seaweed and sea salt! I'll be making some pizzas and I'll need some Seaweed from Coconut Beach. You can collect Salt after draining the water from the glass cans I've put underwater.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Seaweed and sea salt pizza, yum!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for bringing me the ingredients! I'll give some seaweed to Tammy and I'll use the rest to make pizzas.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005t">
	    	<NAME>It's Salty Sand Here</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! I really want to help Izzy with some sand for the sandcastles that she's making for aquariums but I'm busy cleaning up some stuff here. Oh, and she mentioned that she needed some Salt for the water where the salt water fish live. Could you get some Salt from the water in Coconut Beach and collect some lumps of sand?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you know that Izzy builds amazing sandcastles for her aquariums?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, so sweet of you! Thanks for bringing me the sand and the salt - here are some coins for your hard work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<!-- Jim -->
	<QUEST ID="Q006a">
	    	<NAME>Amethyst in the Mist</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there. I'm always on the lookout for rare minerals and gemstones, but today I need something specific. I've heard of some Pandas finding Amethyst in Pawthorne Forest and Small Silver Ore up on Misty Hill. 
Bring me some of each and I'll pay you handsomely for your troubles.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>How's it going with that Amethyst and Small Silver Ore? Is it true there are ghosts on Misty Hill?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
There we go. Look at those beauties! 
Here's some coins for your help. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006b">
	    	<NAME>The Azurite Ring</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, you got time to help out a fellow Panda? I'm supposed to make a custom ring for a client and they specifically asked for gold plating with azurite gemstones. Problem is, I'm all out of azurite and gold.
If you bring me some Azurite Ore from Shady Glen and Small Gold Ore from Harvest Grove, I can pay you for your time. 		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get the gold and azurite yet?
I'm supposed to have the ring ready by tomorrow. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You're back! And you've got the stuff I need, excellent! 
Here's the payment we agreed to.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006c">
	    	<NAME>Silver and Gold (Sans the Gold)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I'm always in need of Silver Ore that I can smelt down and use to make jewelry. Rumor has it there's plenty of Silver Ore to be mined up on Misty Hill. Of course there's also the rumor that Misty Hill is haunted! I'd go myself but, uh, I'm busy.
Think you could bring me 5 Small Silver Ore? You'll need a rock hammer to mine the silver. If you don't have one, I'll sell you one for a fair price.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Had any luck mining that Silver Ore? I'm getting low on silver and people always want more jewelry.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, this will last me a while. 
I hope those ghosts on Misty Hill didn't cause you too much trouble.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006d">
	    	<NAME>Gold Moon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What do you know about Moonstone? It's one of my most popular requests when making custom jewelry for Pandas. It'd be a great help if you could bring me some. Oh, and while you're helping out, might as well bring me a few Small Gold Ore as well.
I hear Pawthorne Forest is a good place to find Moonstone and of course everyone knows about the Small Gold Ore in Harvest Grove, but uh, you didn't hear that from me.		
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Yep, Moonstone is really popular these days. Not really my favorite though. I prefer diamonds.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Let's see what you got. Looks good! You're a hard worker. 
Come by again tomorrow and I might have some more work for you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006e">
	    	<NAME>A Tale of Two Opals</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, wondering if you could help me out? I'm making a bracelet for my sweetheart and I want it to be really special. She loves Opal! Now, the thing to know is that there's a couple kinds of Opal that can be found in Pandanda Land and to make this ring, I'll need both Light Opal and Dark Opal.
What do you say, could you get those for me? The best place to mine for Opal is in Darby Field. Just watch out for those rabbits!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I've got the bracelet crafted, once you bring me the Opal I can set the stones.
You can mine the Opal in Darby Field.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Perfect, these look terrific. This is going to be the best bracelet I've ever made! 
Here's some coins for your help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006f">
	    	<NAME>Finding a Lost Treasure</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Heya, I heard that there was a lost treasure chest in the sea near the Coconut Beach. Could you find it and catch it? After you're ready come and see me, I'll give you half of all the treasure.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The treasure isn't really heavy so I thing you'll be able to take it out of the water with ease. You must be extremely patient!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
500 coins. Nice, here's 250 for you to keep.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006g">
	    	<NAME>Big Catch</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! I'm organizing a fish feast later today and I was wondering if you can catch me something BIG. 3 lobsters and 2 big basses, to be precise. You can catch lobsters at Coconut Beach and Giant Bass could be caught in the Fishing Hole lake.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I know it's plenty of stuff to be caught but I'm sure you'll do it!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, that's now what I call big catch! I'm not a good fisherman, Joe's an expert at it and you seem really good at it as well! Here's some coins for the fish and the lobsters.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006h">
	    	<NAME>Coal and Iron</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
It's always the season of fireplaces. I mean, when it's warm, you need to prepare early fireplaces for the winter and then in the winter, there's need for those. For this reason, I need some coal and iron - 3 lumps of coal from Pawthorne Forest or Misty Hill and 3 small iron ores from Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Uh, I guess it isn't really easy to mine those iron ores, but I'm sure you'll do it.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Good job! I've got enough materials now to start marking those fireplaces. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006i">
	    	<NAME>Gem Collector</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy, could you help me? I want to give my sweetheart Paige some gems as she loves them but I don't have the time. You need to go around and find those giant gems. After you're ready, visit Paige.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm pretty sure you'll find them all, they aren't really hard to find.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Gems? FOR ME? FROM JIM? WOW! I love him! Here's something to thank you for the delivery.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006j">
	    	<NAME>Opals and Amethysts</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Opals and amethysts are nice to find and they've got a nice color. I need 2 Dark Opals, 2 Light Opals and 3 Amethysts. You can find those gems in Bunny Field and Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck with finding the gems? Bunny Field and Pawthorne Forest are the locations where you can mine them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
A nice one, thanks for those.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006k">
	    	<NAME>What's Below the X?</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Psst, come here! Hello, my friend. Do you remember the treasure chest you found the other day? Well, I found a piece of paper inside it and it turns out that it might be a clue for another treasure chest! As far as I can understand, it says that it has been buried in Coconut Beach, however, the ink is too blurry and I can't figure out the exact spot. Do you want to find this treasure? Who knows what it is...
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I know you can find the exact spot! You can do it!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
The clues never fail, neither do you, my fellow treasure hunter! Let's open the treasure chest and celebrate!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006l">
	    	<NAME>Bait Material</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Do you like fishing? I do a lot and my friend Fishy Joe asked me to make some painted bait from silver and gold. Can you bring me 5 Silver Ores from Misty Hill, 5 Gold Ores from Harvest Grove and face paint from any Pandas with an exclamation mark above their head. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
You can mine Silver Ores in Misty Hill and you can mine Gold Ores from Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You're an amazing miner! This will be enough for the bait.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006m">
	    	<NAME>Digging Gold</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day Panda pal! Are you interested to get into a gold digging journey? If that is the case, let's do this - there are 3 treasure chests, full of Panda Gold, the legend says. Why do I need help with that, you'll ask - well, they're very well hidden somewhere around Pandanda. Will you help me out with finding them? 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Those three chests can be literally anywhere - you need to look for them very hard.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Have I ever congratulated you for the amazing skills you have? Let's split the treasure by 2:1 for you, I guess that is more fair than getting a half of it.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006n">
	    	<NAME>What Lurks in the Night</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello there! I've got a special task for you today. I'll need some bauxite from Misty Hill for my upcoming project and I'm really busy sorting some gems here. Will you bring me three ores?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Be careful with all the ghosts on Misty Hill. Could get really hard to mine that bauxite.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for bringing me bauxite. What are you saying? There are strange noises on Misty Hill, more unusual than usual? That's weird, can you bring me a sound recording from Misty Hill, The Parlour and Haunted Hallway?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006o">
	    	<NAME>What Lurks in the Night</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I could try helping you out with finding out what's wrong there, but I'll need sound recordings from Misty Hill and The Parlour.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
More unusual noises than the usual ones around the Haunted Hause? What? That is worth investigating.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Apparently, they are coming from the Haunted Hallway - it's the noisiest there. Could it be that random ghost of a monster?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006p">
	    	<NAME>What Lurks in the Night</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I think that we're getting to the bottom of this story - it is most likely the the ghost of the monster of the Haunted House - unless it's another ghost, of course.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Be careful - that ghost may be really angry and try possessing you!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
That ghost must've been another one that's haunting the House! Good job on catching him. Now, what else is there?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006q">
	    	<NAME>Equinox</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello, my fellow. Do you know when it's the Equinox? It's when the day and the night are of the same length, when the light and the darkness are balanced! We'll need to balance the gems for a perfect magical jewelry - we'll need 5 Silver Ores from Misty Hill and 5 Amethysts from Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The light is what unites and the required thing that balances the forces. Same applies for the darkness.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
It's the Equinox today and it's the only time when this special piece of jewelry can get magical powers.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006r">
	    	<NAME>Love Beyond the Bones</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings... You are asking, why am I so sad? I'm in love with Trixie, the magical Dragon Master. She appears and disappears mysteriously. I suppose she's a Panda out of this world, and I really hope that if this is the case, her favorite flowers are the Ghostflowers. Will you be able to pick 10 of them from the dangerous Misty Hill?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Oh my dear Trixie, she may really be an extraterrestrial... and might not even love me...
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you for the great help - I'm going to try summoning Trixie with a special Dragon I got from her.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<!-- Dan -->
	<QUEST ID="Q007a">
	    	<NAME>Flaky Crust is a Must</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ummm, you know what would make today even better? Some homemade apple turnovers! Those tender apples and cinnamon in a flaky crust, my mouth is watering already!
All I'd need is a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned, a few Small Brown Eggs from his barn, and 2 Juicy Apples which I'm sure you can find in the Orchard. Think you could handle that?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'd sure appreciate you getting me those items so I could make my apple turnovers. Wrangling these bunnies really works up my appetite!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ahh, that's the stuff! These will make a splendid dessert!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007b">
	    	<NAME>Bye Bye Blackberry</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You know what's better than blackberry pie? Me neither. Of course it takes the freshest ingredients to make the freshest pies. 
Think you could rustle up some Blackberries from Harvest Grove, a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned and a Small Brown Egg from his Barn? 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I sure do appreciate your help today. Nice to know there's helpful Pandas around like yourself.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well that was speedy! Here's some coins to cover the cost of the flour.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007c">
	    	<NAME>Peachy Keen</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Do you like peaches? I do! And I make a great Peach Cobbler if I do say so myself! Of course, I'll need a few items before I can bake some up.
I reckon I'll need a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned, a couple of Small Brown Eggs from Ned's Barn, and 2 Fuzzy Peaches from the Orchard. Could you help me out?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you get those items for the Peach Cobbler? My stomach is rumblin'!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Aye now, those look mighty fresh! Me and my stomach thank you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007d">
	    	<NAME>Famous Blueberry Pie</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I'm making my famous Farmer Dan Blueberry Pie but I'm missing a few ingredients and haven't had time to go shopping. Would you be a true friend and get them for me?
Let's see, I'll need a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned, a Small Brown Egg from his Barn, and 3 Hardy Blueberries from Harvest Grove. I think that should do it. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you find the pie ingredients I need? Umm, I can taste it already!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yee haw, those look tasty! I hope it wasn't too difficult to get them. 
Here's a few coins for your help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007e">
	    	<NAME>Bring Home the Rhubarb</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
The Missus wants me to bring home some items so she can make a rhubarb pie for dessert. It's not my favorite but I can't complain when she's doing the cookin'.  
You have time to fetch a few items for me? I reckon I'll need a Small Brown Egg from Farmer Ned's Barn, some Rhubarb from Harvest Grove, and a Small Bag of Flour. Farmer Ned will have that for sale.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Don't be too long getting those items. I'll be in a heap of trouble if I go home empty handed.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ahh, you're a life saver you are. These are just what I needed.
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007f">
	    	<NAME>Bunnies on a Diet</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I've been noticing my bunnies acting a bit sluggish lately. Think it's time to mix up their diet with a new mixture of vegetables. Do you have time to help me out?
I need a Large Radish and 2 Red Cabbage from Harvest Grove and a few Purple Carrots which you can find right here in Darby Field. I'll blend them together for the bunnies myself.		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to get all the vegetables for my new bunny diet mix? I can't have them sleeping all day!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yee haw, this will do nicely! I appreciate your help and I'm sure the bunnies will as well.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007g">
	    	<NAME>Runaway Bunnies</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! Thanks for noticing my need for help. Recently, some of my bunnies have escaped and even the bunny chasers couldn't catch them! Pretty sure they're around here, or they've may hopped on to Pawthorne Forest or in Farmer Ned's properties. But first, you'll need some carrots! Go collect 5 of each kind of carrots here and in Harvest Grove.		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
The bunnies might go way too far to be found and those are my favorite ones! Remember, the Purple Carrot can be found only here.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yee haw, this will do nicely! I appreciate your help and I'm sure the bunnies will as well. Now you need to find them all - they are around Darby Field and Harvest Grove. They're shy so they might hide behind patches of grass! Oh, and just a reminder, they don't go to urban areas and surely aren't in Shady Glen as they don't like big rocks.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007h">
			<NAME>Runaway Bunnies</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Yee haw, this will do nicely! I appreciate your help and I'm sure the bunnies will as well. Now you need to find them all - they are around Darby Field and Harvest Grove. They're shy so they might hide behind patches of grass! Oh, and just a reminder, they don't go to urban areas and surely aren't in Shady Glen as they don't like big rocks.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found my favorite bunnies yet? I don't know what I will do without them! One of them is very rare and is my favorite bunny.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Oh my god, thanks a lot! They're safe and sound! Those are my favorite ones and I do love them a lot. Here's a reward for your good deed.
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007i">
			<NAME>Pumpkin Pie</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Heya! As you may know, I'm a pie lover and I enjoy experimenting with different types of pie. Today, I'll be making a pumpkin pie - I'll need 3 Pumpkins from Harvest Grove or Shady Glen, I'll also need 1 Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned and 2 Rhubarbs.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to harvest some rhubarb? I heard that there weren't many left.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the ingredients, now I can make my pumpkin pie. Stop by later for a piece!
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007j">
			<NAME>Peach Cookies</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I decided to make some peach cookies today. They look just like real peaches, but rather, they've got pastry and some peach jam inside. I'll need 2 brown eggs, 3 peaches and 1 bag of flour. Could you bring me all this?
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Peach cookies are really tasty, I just need you to bring me 2 brown eggs, 3 peaches and 1 bag of flour.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Here's one for you as well! I'll now be able to make peach cookies for everybody.
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007k">
			<NAME>A Bouquet of Roses</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC024</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
I really love my sweet darling Maggie. I want to make a surprise for her - a bouquet of roses. I'd like to ask you if you can collect some roses and bring them to Maggie... She'll love them! You can find roses only in Darby Field.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Maggie really loves roses, so hurry up and collect the roses for her.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
A BOUQUET OF ROSES? FOR ME? FROM FARMER DAN? AWWW, THAT'S REALLY CUTEEEEE!
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007l">
			<NAME>Snack for Maggie's Horses</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC024</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
As you may know, I really love Maggie, Farmer Ned's sister. I'd like to give some apples and carrots for her horses, which are her favorite and are petlike for her. Anyhow, could you collect some for me?
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm sure Maggie's horses will love fresh apples and fresh carrots.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Is that for my horses? Thanks! Oh, what are you saying? They're by Farmer Dan? Thanks, tell him I love him too!
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007m">
			<NAME>Honey and Pumpkins Dessert</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Do you know what one of my favorite desserts is? Yes, Honey and Pumpkins. I'd like to make some today. Could you bring me some honey from Pawthorne Forest and pumpkins from Harvest Grove? I'll definitely pay you later.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Honey can be found in Pawthorne Forest. Pumpkins usually grow in Harvest Grove and I have seen some in Shady Glen as well.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
These will make a sick Honey and Pumpkins dessert. Here's some coins for you.
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007n">
			<NAME>Bunny Issues Again</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Heya! Ahhh finally, after the last repairs, I think the bunnies wont escape again from the cage... *screech* Not agaaaain... While the other Pandas are trying to catch the bunnies, can you bring me 5 iron strings and a padlock? You can buy a Padlock from Mr. Elmhurst, and the Iron Strings may be found in the big squares.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
I'll need 5 iron strings, which are usually dropped in the big squares and a padlock from Mr. Elmhurst.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the help, Panda, gotta start working! And please, watch out for those bunnies! They always manage to escape...
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007o">
			<NAME>With the Speed of Sound</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Howdy buddy - have you seen an odd bunny running around mPandanda? Well, I guess you didn't - you'd know for sure if you saw it. It's a blue bunny that is capable of running like no other bunny I have seen in my life! Some of my fellas spotted this Sonic speed furry 'round, causing lots of trouble. Will you find it and catch it?
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
That bunny won't be in urban areas for sure. Check locations like Pawthorne Forest, Shady Glen and so on. Bunnies are afraid of Pandas, y'know.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Gotcha! I'm sure this little furry didn't mean to cause any troub-- Ouch! He bit me! 
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007p">
			<NAME>Mystic and Real</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC024</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Hey there fella! As you have probably heard from the rumors around, I'm in love with Maggie. I'd love to give her something special. I've been thinking about it for a few days and I've decided that it's going to be a combination of something mystic and real - Ghostflowers and Tulips. Can you get 4 of those mystic flowers from Misty Hill and 3 of the real ones from The Orchard?
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
That's the best present for her and she'll really love it! 
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Farmer Dan is sending this beautiful mix of flowers to me? Oh my, I love him so much, thanks for bringing me the flowers!
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007q">
			<NAME>Bunny Food</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
G'day bunny chaser! How's your day going, how many bunnies have you caught? Those little ruffians, they're always hungry from that running away and I really need to feed them very often. I'll be busy making a new bunny cage here so I'd love it if you could bring me 3 Potatoes from Harvest Grove and pick me the freshest three Purple Carrots and the best four Yellow Carrots from Darby Field.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Taking care of those bunnies is extremely hard, ugh. I really need to hire somebody to look after them.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the help, you're a true friend! I'm already sick of picking all those carrots and potatoes.
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007r">
			<NAME>Planting Carrots</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Hey, howdy, how are you doing? Have you heard about the party later, will you be going? I surely will! But first, I've got some urgent work here to be done and then I need to plant some carrots. Will you plant some for me in The Orchard, Harvest Grove and then come back here in Darby Field to plant them?
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
Planting carrots can be real fun especially if you listen to music.
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Yay, now whenever the bunnies escape they can dig some food and feed themselves. I can't really pick carrots constantly.
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007s">
			<NAME>The Quest for the Bunnyfish</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC004</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Heyo! The other day Joe and I argued about a new species of fish called Bunnyfish. He said that he hadn't seen one around mPandanda Land and he didn't want to believe me that I almost had caught one near Coconut Beach. I believe the fishermen that use Pierre the Pirate's boat docked near Lighthouse Island have found some as well, so check there.
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm sure the Bunnyfish exists! Patience is the key!
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Seems like Farmer Dan was right! The Bunnyfish actually exists! You're invited to the fish party tonight, we'll prepare a new tasty dish with the Bunnyfish!
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007t">
			<NAME>Chili Taste</NAME>
			<START>NPC010</START>
			<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
			<END>NPC010</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! What did you eat today? I haven't eaten much and I really want to eat something tasty for dinner later. Hmm, I'd like to try a special Chili and Potatoes dish, I'm up for something really hot! Will you bring me two Potatoes and two Chili Peppers from Harvest Grove?
			</TEXTSTART>
			<TEXTACTIVE>
After you bring me the Chili Peppers and the Potatoes feel free to come over and try how HOT my Chili and Potato dish could be!
			</TEXTACTIVE>
			<TEXTEND>
Ay, thanks! Yum, it's now time to cook this hot dish.
			</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>


	<!-- Izzy -->
	<QUEST ID="Q008a">
	    	<NAME>Wall of Fish</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I've been thinking about adding some new fish to my giant wall tank here in the store.  More brightly colored fish would really spruce up the place.
Could you head over to Coconut Beach and catch me some Orange Clownfish, Regal Tang, and Yellow Longnose Butterfly fish? They would make a great addition to my collection!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>My aquarium really needs a makeover. Have you caught any fish for me?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Cool! These fish are just what I needed. Now I just need to clean out the tank. 
Have some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008b">
	    	<NAME>Top Dollar Fish</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, glad you stopped by! Mr. Elmhurst was in the other day looking for some new fish for his aquarium. I know he would pay top dollar for them.
If you'd like to make a few coins, catch a Yellow Longnose Butterfly fish from Coconut Beach, then head over to the Fishing Hole and catch 3 Calico Goldfish and a Violet Perch. Once you have all the fish take them to Mr. Elmhurst on West Market Street.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I know Mr. Elmhurst will be really excited to get those fish. 
If you need a fishing pole, Fishy Joe sells them for a fair price.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, wonderful! I can't wait to add these to my aquarium. 
Here's some coins for the fish.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008c">
	    	<NAME>Fish for Fitch</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC008</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh dear! The proprietor of Clothing Co., Fitch, has ordered some new fish for an aquarium he just bought but I don't have the fish he wanted!
I tell you what, if you take him 2 Golden Addis Butterfly fish, 2 Regal Tang, and a Black Angelfish you can keep the coins he gives you. You can catch the Gold Addis and the Regal Tang from Coconut Beach and the others from the Fishing Hole.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you catch those fish for Fitch yet? Don't forget to collect the coins he owes for them.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
My new fish! They look great! Tell Izzy I said thanks! 
Oh, and here's the coins I owe her.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008d">
	    	<NAME>Fish Make Great Gifts</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Do you know McWiggles who runs the Ice Cream Shop? He wanted to buy some fish for his daughter Lisa as a surprise. Let's see, he was interested in getting a few Maroon Clownfish, an Orange Clownfish, and some Violet Perch for her.
I'm sure you can catch the clownfish from Coconut Beach but you'll want to head to the Fishing Hole to catch the perch. Once you have the fish, take them over to McWiggles in the Ice Cream Shop. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Once you've caught the fish take them over to McWiggles at The Big Scoop. I'm sure he'll want to wrap them up.	    	
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh my! These fish are terrific! I'm sure Lisa will love these.
Let's hope she takes good care of them.	    	
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008e">
	    	<NAME>Clowns and Angels</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! Would you have some time to help me replenish some of my fish supply? The clownfish and angelfish are flying off the shelves! I can hardly keep them in stock.
I need 2 Orange Clownfish which can be caught from Coconut Beach and 3 Black Angelfish from over at the Fishing Hole. Hurry back, I'll probably have them sold by the time you return.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you caught any of the fish I need? I do hate to send customers home empty handed.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Great timing! I have a customer coming in this afternoon to pick them up! 
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008f">
	    	<NAME>Reading is Fun</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! Apart from keeping pets in my treehouse where Pandas come and buy, I have another hobby - reading. I know that there are usually some lost books that you look for, so I'd like some copies of these. If you don't know what's inside Paige's Book, there are some useful tips for our lifestyle here, but I lost my copy.
Could you find all those 5 books and bring them to me?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I enjoy reading. I can't wait to see what you're going to bring me!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Those books look interesting! And you've also brought me Paige's Book with the life hacks! Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008g">
	    	<NAME>Paper Modelling</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I've got one fun activity that I do when I'm bored - I make stuff using old paper. I need some paper to craft something real quick. Could you bring me some old newspapers and some glue?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I enjoy making paper stuff. Have you found any old newspapers yet?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
I think that I already know what I'm going to make. Thanks for the materials!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008h">
	    	<NAME>Feathers for a Pillow</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! I've been getting too little sleep lately... I guess it's my pillow. Could you find some feathers so that I can make myself a new one?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Ugh, that old pillow... I need you to find me some feathers for a pillow.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
These feathers looks soft, thanks for finding them!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008i">
	    	<NAME>Colorful Chicken Eggs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I heard that there have been found some interesting and rare colorful chicken eggs around the island. Colorful eggs which change their color depending on the light can be found everywhere, whereas the rest can be found in the hens' nests in Farmer Ned's Barn.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you found any colorful eggs yet? I've only heard about them, but I'm not sure if they really exist.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Those indeed look interesting! I gotta wait and see when the chicken will hatch... Who knows, maybe even colored chicken!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008j">
	    	<NAME>Lost Aquarium Pieces</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! I ordered some aquariums online a few days ago but it turned out that all the crates got lost and additionally, the aquariums aren't assembled. Would you help me finding those crates? You have to wait for the crates to appear as they haven't arrived yet. Oh, and I'd also need you to find some water-resistant glue.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I know that one of them ended up in McWiggles' shop, but I'm not sure where did the rest go. You have to wait for the crates to appear as they haven't arrived yet.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Awesome work! I can finally get the pieces together and make new aquariums where I can keep my fish.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008k">
	    	<NAME>Mushroom Soup</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! I love mushroom soup a lot, don't you too? I'd like to have some right now. But, I can't go out to find some mushrooms. Would you do this for me? They can be found in Darby Field, Pawthorne Forest, Harvest Grove and Shady Glen.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Mm, can't wait to eat some mushroom soup! I can't wait for you to bring me some mushrooms! They can be found in Darby Field, Pawthorne Forest, Harvest Grove and Shady Glen.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Mm, look at those beauties! I gotta do that soup real quick. Thanks for the ingredients!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008l">
	    	<NAME>Hungry Dragons</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
HOLLA! How's your day going pet lover? Anything new? Sadly, I'm running out of dragon food. This is the worst time for ingredients for Flint Nibbles to be out of stock! Now that every Panda has a lot of dragons, I have a ton of hungry little beasts outside my shop, waiting for the moment to eat me alive! Since I cant go outside, please help me and bring me ingredients for their favorite snack: Ill need a bunch of Chili Peppers from Harvest Grove; some Salmon from Coconut Beach; an Onion and a Potato.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Those hungry dragons, oh my! Ill need a bunch of Chili Peppers from Harvest Grove; some Salmon from the ocean; an Onion and a Potato.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks! Now that my mischevious little disasters are owned by a lot of Pandas, I should really consider cooking more frequently!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008m">
	    	<NAME>Pet Aid</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! We need some help with the pets in the Pet Store and a lot of them get hurt often. I guess Pandas aren't very careful when having fun with their little fellas. Could you help me out by finding a lost First Aid Kit and a Spool of Thread?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Those little cuties get hurt easily and they should be looked after with lots of care.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for helping us out here in the Pet Shop, now let me help that little cute fella over there!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008n">
	    	<NAME>Pineapple Pet Chairs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
How are you doing fella? How's your pet-tastic day? Do you wanna make our buddies happy? I'm up to making some little cute pineapple chairs for them. Will you bring me 3 Pineapples which you can find in The Orchard and Harvest Grove and a tube of Glue, located somewhere indoors?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>We may even start giving away pineapple chairs to pet owners alongside heat lamps!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Nice one, thanks for the materials! Come back later for one little cute chair!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008o">
	    	<NAME>Sandy and Sparkly</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Hey, have you ever taken part in a pet show? I have done so a few times and now it's time to shine again with some little cuties from the Pet Shop - literally! Will you find me some Moon Sand and water-resistant glue? If you want, you can join my team for the show later.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Pet shows are always really interesting and this year we'll surely have the chance to win.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAY! WE WON IT! THANK YOU SO MUCH! We had the best sparkly costumes!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008p">
	    	<NAME>Cake for the Moon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Hello! Do you remember the pet show we took part in recently? Well, now we've got some guests coming up for a party in the Pet Shop and I'm going to be preparing my favorite Moon Cake that even our little dragons can eat. Will you bring me some Moon Sand from Bear Hollow or Shady Glen, a Quart of Cream from Farmer Dan and 2 Sugar Beets from The Orchard?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Moon Cake is the most delicious cake you'll ever taste, I'm sure you'll like it a lot!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the ingredients! Join in the party at 5pm!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008q">
	    	<NAME>Blue Blueberry Dragons</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
G'day dragon pal! Little dragons want to be painted and to change their color, something Pandas can do. Today we'll be experimenting and who knows, we may be selling Pet Paint one day! So we'll need 5 Blackberries and 5 Blueberries from Harvest Grove as well as some newspapers that you can find in the large squares.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I'm interested to see what the outcome will be - will we have the right paint?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Now it's time to mix the blueberries and the blackberries and see what's it going to look like. Thanks for the help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008r">
	    	<NAME>Readers' Meeting</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
			<TEXTSTART>
Howdy fellow! Since Izzy is too busy in the Pet Shop she asked me to help out with the planning of her Readers' Meeting. Will you help us with that? I'll be bringing some ice cream and fruit, could you give around to our friend Farmer Dan and the rest cupcakes with invitations and find some Pen the Pig games to play?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>On the Readers' Meeting we will be discussing some books we have read - my favorite is 'The Princess and the Panda' and then we will be playing some games and eating ice cream.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, thanks for inviting Pandas and bringing the games! Join us in the Readers' Meeting later if you want to share some thoughts about your favorite book.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

<!-- Maggie -->
	<QUEST ID="Q009a">
	    	<NAME>Watch Your Step</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I sure could use some help if you don't mind getting your paws dirty. All these horses around town have been making a bit of a smell, if you know what I mean. 
Think you could stop by Bear Hollow, East and West Market Street and do a little sanitation clean up? Head on back here when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How's that horse clean up going? I'd hate for any pandas to accidentally step in something.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Got the towns all cleaned up? I'm sure everyone appreciates having clean streets to walk on. Just be sure to wash your paws!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009b">
	    	<NAME>Horses Wear Shoes Too</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Glad you stopped by. My horses need new shoes! Jim is going to make some for me but needs the raw materials first. Would you be interested in gathering some Small Iron Ore and Small Bauxite Ore for me? 
Once you have them take the ore over to Jim on West Market Street and he'll know what to do. You'll find the iron in Harvest Grove and the bauxite at Misty Hill.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you gathered the iron and bauxite ore yet? Take them over to Jim on West Market Street when you have them.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, these must be for the horse shoes Maggie needs. Great, I'll be able to make a lot of shoes from this much ore.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009c">
	    	<NAME>Where's the Hay?</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey darling, would you like to help me out? I was supposed to get a delivery of hay bales but when the tractor showed up the hay bales were gone. They must have fallen off along the way.
Could you go out and look for the Hay Bales? If you can find them and bring them to me I'll make sure you're rewarded with some coins.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Any luck finding those Hay Bales? They must have fallen off the tractor outside somewhere.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Super, you found them all! I knew I could count on such a wonderful Panda as you.
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009d">
	    	<NAME>Equine Snacks</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there, glad you stopped by. I like to feed my horses a special treat every now and then. They get tired of eating oats all time.
Would you go out and get me 3 Fresh Apples and 2 Nutritious Carrots? You'll find the apples at the Orchard and Darby Field has some of the best carrots around. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Hey, did you get the Fresh Apples and Nutritious Carrots yet? My horses will be thrilled to get a tasty snack.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Back so soon? These look fantastic! My horses and I thank you for your help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009e">
	    	<NAME>Ingredients for Farmer Dan</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey buddy! I love my boyfriend, Farmer Dan, and I know he's keen on making pies. I decided to make a surprise for him and bring him some ingredients. Could you get him a Fresh Apple, some Rhubarb and some Peaches? Thanks in advance!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I'm sure Farmer Dan will use the products since they're fresh and what's more, he loves making pies!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, ingredients for my pies from Maggie? Thanks a lot! Tell her that I love her!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009f">
	    	<NAME>Dirt Cleaner</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day cowmaster! I got lots of reports that there's dirt around the island. Could you clean all the lumps up? You need to wait in order to see a lump of dirt 'cause I already cleaned some of them, but they appear regularly.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How's the clean-up going?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Goodie, you cleaned all the dirt up. Thanks for the help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009g">
	    	<NAME>Open Fire Feast</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy partner! I decided to make a feast for my pals, so we'll sit around a campfire and roast some fish for dinner. Could you help me? I'll need 3 Large Trouts and 3 Catfish from Fishing Hole and some Salmon from the sea.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Hay! Have you got those fish yet?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
That's enough fish, thanks a lot buddy.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009h">
	    	<NAME>Fresh Cut Grass</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! As you see, I've got a lot of herbivorous animals, but I've been recently short on grass. May you cut some for me from Darby Field and Harvest Grove?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>My animals would definitely love to eat some fresh grass.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, that's a lot of fresh-cut grass! You're an amazing animal friend!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009i">
	    	<NAME>Finding Old Boots</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! I've been on some expeditions to the Fishing Hole lake and I've been looking for the friendly monster recently. It's just like the monster from the Loch Ness lake on the nearby island! Though, I've lost quite a lot of boots. Can you fish them all?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Well I guess those boots won't disappear from the Fishing Hole lake, so keep throwing your rod there.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well done, they've even got some mold, haha. Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009j">
	    	<NAME>Quick Help</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! You got here just in time! I don't know how this happened, I was teaching a kid to ride a pony, when suddenly he fell to the ground! Poor kid, he is really scared and hurt, but I don't remember where I left the first aid kit... While I stay here to calm him down and look after him, can you please find my kit?  
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I have no idea where I could have left my first aid kit, I'm sorry, you'll have to look everywhere.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You're a life saver, thanks! Let me put the bandage... and... done! Look, I think you have just made a new friend! You can stay here with him while I contact his family... and of course I will mention you! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009k">
	    	<NAME>A Sweet Surprise</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ey buddy, so nice to see you again! I want to make a surprise for my boyfriend, Farmer Dan, and treat him with a fruity dessert he loves. I'll need you to collect five peaches and a sugar beet from The Orchard, two eggs from my hens here and a bag of flour from Farmer Ned outside. And, please, don't tell Ned why do you need the flour, I don't want anybody to know about my surprise.  
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Yey, I bet Dan will like my sweet surprise!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Sweet, thank you! I'll now get this surprise ready and I'll make my boyfriend happy after a long day fixing the bunnies' cage.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009l">
	    	<NAME>The Lost Pony</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I'm glad you're here! My pony Dubliner managed to escape again from The Barn! He is a good companion, but he's always so energetic and adventurous that he went on a free ride this morning and perhaps he's got lost. Could you find him? Maybe if you follow his footsteps you would have luck.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>He doesn't go to urban places, so don't worry.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hmm, sounds interesting! Let's analyse the footsteps. Could you ask Jim where you could find Dubliner?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009m">
	    	<NAME>The Lost Pony</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hmm, sounds interesting! Let's analyse the footsteps. Could you ask Jim where you could find Dubliner?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>You need to talk to Jim so that we could know better where Dubliner is hiding.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Haha, that pony of Maggie always gets lost! No worries, it won't be hard to find him. Check out Abandoned Island, Darby Field, Fishing Hole, The Orchard and Shady Glen, he must be in one of those locations.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009n">
	    	<NAME>The Lost Pony</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Haha, that pony of Maggie always gets lost! No worries, it won't be hard to find him. Check out Abandoned Island, Darby Field, Fishing Hole, The Orchard and Shady Glen, he must be in one of those locations.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Check out Abandoned Island, Darby Field, Fishing Hole, The Orchard and Shady Glen, Dubliner must be there.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, thank you so much for returning my lost pony Dubliner! Here are some coins.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009o">
	    	<NAME>Feeding the Cow</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day fella! We've got to feed the cow in here, will you help? Will you find 5 Hay Bales? Some Pandas have reported that a lot of them have ended up too far from mPandanda Land.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Cow's favorite food? That's hay!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the help - would you like to feed her?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009p">
	    	<NAME>Feeding the Chicken</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
CUAK! These chicken over there, you know them? Yeah, they give a lot of eggs but need to be fed very often. I'm busy cleaning up around, can you find some Grass and Worms to feed them?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Chicken's favorite grass is a very special one that can cut your paw. Be careful!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
That's enough, thank you so much! Come later to pick a colorful egg that has been laid recently.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009q">
	    	<NAME>Keeping it Safe</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello Stable Master! How's your day going? We've lost yet another pony and we're lost even, haha. Farmer Ned and I will be setting up a wire-netting. This is why we'll need 5 long Iron Strings and a Padlock from Mr. Elmhurst.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Setting the wire-netting is really urgent - we need to prevent other ponies from escaping!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Just on time, thanks for the materials! We'll also put bells on the ponies but that's going to be later.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009r">
	    	<NAME>Barn Repairs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC014</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey fellow farmer! Have you noticed that the roof of the Barn is leaking? Yeah, some planks have been broken by the wind recently. We'll need some Wood, a Hammer and a Box of Nails in order to repair it. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Repairing the roof of the Barn is urgent - otherwise, whenever it rains, everything is going to be underwater, haha.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the materials! I'm getting on the roof now, wish me luck with the repairs!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009s">
	    	<NAME>Horse Shoes Mean Luck</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello! I've only recently noticed that our ponies lose so many of their shoes that Pandas take them and keep them for luck. However, I've also seen that there are so many that are just lying on the ground, lost most likely, that I have decided that they may be of use again. Will you help me out with finding them all?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Pandas really believe that horse shoes bring luck. I doubt this. But they definitely are lucky for our horses!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh, you've found plenty of them, thank you! Here's a small thank-you prize for your good work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Halloween -->
	<QUEST ID="Q051a">
	    	<NAME>Eyes on the Prize</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC016</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC016</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC016</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Boo! Ah, I see you don't frighten easily. Good, I am in need of your assistance. I find that I am running low on Ghoul Eyes. What do I need them for? Never you mind. Suffice it to say, I need them and that should be good enough for you. 
If you bring me 5 Ghoul Eyes I will reward you for your service. You should readily find Ghoul Eyes in Pawthorne Forest or Misty Hill.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you returned with my Ghoul Eyes? No? Well then, might I suggest you go and look for them. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Splendid, splendid! These will do nicely. 
Ah yes, enjoy these coins for a such a fine job.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q051b">
	    	<NAME>Wicked Brew</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC016</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC016</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC016</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, you again! Surely, you have time to help me? I have several cauldrons dispersed throughout these lands that need attending. Take these items and add them to each of the cauldrons. 
There are 5 cauldrons in all and I'll know if you skip one, so do not try to trick me. Hurry now, do this for me and return when you are done!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you attended all of my cauldrons yet? Make sure you add those ingredients evenly in each one. 
Return to me when you have finished.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, you have returned. I trust there were no problems? Of course not, you're an honest Panda.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q051c">
	    	<NAME>Bat Wing Stew</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC016</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC016</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC016</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings Panda! Perhaps you could help me? I'm preparing a Spicy Bat Wing Stew for my fellow ghosts. And I'm in dire need of more bat wings! 
You will find bats often asleep hanging from buildings and other large structures. Bring me 4 Bats for my concoction and some Strong Spices from your Farmer Ned. Go now, time is of the essence!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I need those bat wings and spices! If they aren't added at the right time they stew will be ruined!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, just in the nick of time. I underestimated you, Panda. You are trustworthy indeed!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<QUEST ID="Q051d">
	    	<NAME>Chocolate Bars</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! With all these Pandas out trick or treating for  candy, sometimes their pumpkins overflow and candy drops onto the ground. 
I like all candy but Chocolate Bars are my favorite. If you find any Chocolate Bars as you're walking around Pandanda, I'll trade you some coins for them.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you find any Chocolate Bars? You should find them on the ground just like the Halloween candy hidden around Pandanda.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! You're a great friend for getting these for me. Here's the coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q051e">
	    	<NAME>Peanut Butter Bars</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I've got a confession to make. I love Peanut Butter Bars. The way they mix that perfect balance of chocolate and peanut butter, ummm, ummm!
If you happen to come across any Peanut Butter Bars while you're out looking for candy, I'd sure appreciate it you could bring me some. You can find Peanut Butter Bars anywhere you find other candy.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How's the search going? I can't wait to bite in to a Peanut Butter Bar. I'm sure you can find some mixed in with all the other candy placed around Pandanda.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wonderful! I'll enjoy these after dinner. Take some coins for the candy.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q051f">
	    	<NAME>Caramel Bars</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC008</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC008</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC008</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! I've seen Pandas wearing some really great costumes this year. But Halloween is just about dressing up in costumes, it's about candy too! Umm, there's not anything much better than a Caramel Bar!
Would you collect 5 Caramel Bars for me? I'm sure with all the trick or treating going on you'll find plenty. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you find any Caramel Bars? You should be able to find them any place where you find Halloween candy.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh boy, look at those mouth watering Caramel Bars! Thanks so much for your help.
Here's a few coins for helping out.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Thanksgiving / Christmas -->
	<QUEST ID="Q055a">
	    	<NAME>Turkey Feathers</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi there! I've been try to collect turkey feathers to make a ceremonial headdress but at this rate I won't have enough. 
If you happen to come across any Turkey Feathers as you travel around Pandanda please pick them up and bring them to me. You'd be helping me out a lot and I'll be glad to pay you for them.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had any luck finding the Turkey Feathers? I won't be able to complete my headdress without them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! You're a great friend for getting these for me. 
Here's the coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q055b">
	    	<NAME>Apple Cider</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I heard McWiggles is planning to make some of his famous apple cider. It's a great way to keep warm on a cold autumn evening and tastes great! I know he  could use some more apples if you're not busy.
I'm sure if you took him 4 Small Apples from the Orchard and some Cinnamon Spice, he'd reward you for your help. Farmer Ned should have Cinnamon Spice for sale this time of year.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you collected the apples and cinnamon for McWiggles yet? I can't wait for him to make more of that delicious apple cider.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, thank you! I was just about to make a new batch of apple cider and was running low on supplies. 
Enjoy these coins for all your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q055c">
	    	<NAME>Pumpkin Pie</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
It's the holiday season here in Pandanda and I like to bake up some homemade Pumpkin Pie to help celebrate. If you're up for a little work, I'll need some Small Pumpkins, Cinnamon Spice, and a Medium Sugar Beet to get started. 
You'll find the best Small Pumpkins over in Harvest Grove or Shady Glen and I'm sure Farmer Ned has some Cinnamon Spice for sale. Sugar Beets can be found in the Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get me those ingredients yet? Pumpkin Pie waits for no Panda, or so they say. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ahh, those look like some might fine pumpkins! This may be my best pie yet! Much obliged!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q055d">
	    	<NAME>Chilly The Snowman</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC019</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Have you spoken with Chilly the Snowman yet? He needs a constant supply of new snowballs to keep him looking his best.
If you find any good mounds of snow around be sure to create some snowballs and take them to him. You can find him on East Market Street.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you collect any snowballs for Chilly? I'd hate to see him melt away!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
More snowballs! I'll just stick those right over here. 
Ah, I'm feeling better now. Thank you! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Christmas -->
	<QUEST ID="Q056a">
	    	<NAME>Tree Delivery</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, greetings! I wonder if you could help me spread some holiday cheer around Pandanda Land. I have a bunch of trees that need to be set up and you look like just the Panda to help.
Deliver these trees to Clothing Co., The Purple Door, The Den, Book Nook, Farmer Ned's Barn, and The Big Scoop. There should be tree stands on the floor where you need to place them. Come back to me when you're done for your reward.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you delivered those trees yet? I'm sure they will add lots of festive cheer for everyone who sees them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
So you got them all set up? Great work! Here's some coins to show my appreciation.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q056b">
	    	<NAME>The Missing Ornaments</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings to you! Would you happen to have a few minutes to spare? I was gathering all my tree ornaments and it appears I may have lost a few of them. 
I would be greatly obliged if you could take a look around Pandanda for the ornaments and bring me any that you stumble upon. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck find my lost tree decorations? I would start by searching Pawthorne Forest. The trees won't be nearly as festive without decorations.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah ha! Fantastic, you've found them. I knew you could do it!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q056c">
	    	<NAME>Decorating The Trees</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Happy Holidays! I hope you're getting into the holiday spirit. Would you mind helping me decorate some of the trees around Pandanda?
Here, take these ornaments and place them on the trees in Clothing Co., The Purple Door, The Den, Book Nook, Farmer Ned's Barn, and The Big Scoop. Return to me once you've finished and I'll reward you with some coins.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
How's the tree decorating going? I hope they spread some cheer to other Pandas!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Done already? You're a very speedy helper! Here's some coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- March of the Snowmen -->
	<QUEST ID="Q060a">
	    	<NAME>Snow Fort Reinforcements!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, greetings! With all the snowmen running around here, I figure it's safest to stay in this snow fort. Trouble is, it takes a lot of snow to maintain. Maybe you could help me out with that.
We'll need some Snow Blocks to reinforce the walls. The best way to make a Snow Block is to find a nice lump of snow and shape it out of that. Bring me 5 Snow Blocks and I'll make it worth your time.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had any luck finding the Snow Blocks? This fort won't last very long with out reinforcements.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, you've done me a huge favor friend and I won't soon forget it.
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q060b">
	    	<NAME>Keep the Fires Burning</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I've been put in charge of making sure there's plenty of firewood for the fire pits at the Fishing Hole and Coconut Beach. It's a big job and I could use a little help if you've got the time.
I still need a little more Firewood and some Newspaper that I could use as kindling. You'll find Firewood in Pawthorne Forest and probably some Newspaper Kindling in one of the towns.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you collected the Firewood and Newspaper Kindling yet? I know there's going to be a lot of Pandas around the fire pits tonight!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! I'll deliver these to make sure all the Pandas stay warm tonight. 
Here's coins for all your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q061a">
	    	<NAME>Snowman Accessories</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Isn't all this snow wonderful? I'm thinking about building some snowmen but I still need some items to dress them. 
I'll need some Charcoal which can be found in Pawthorne Forest or Misty Hill and a Carrot from Darby Field. I left my Scarf in the Book Nook that could be used and I remember seeing a Top Hat in the Den Tree House in Pawthorne Forest. I knew you would help me!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get the decorations for the snowmen yet? I'll wait until you return before I start building them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks! You're a true friend. I'll get started on the snowmen first thing tomorrow!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q061b">
	    	<NAME>X Marks the Snowman</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey again! I was just about to go out and build some snowmen. Would you want to help out? 
I've marked out places in the locations where I want to build them. Maybe you could go ahead and get started? Head to Darby Field first so you'll know what to look for. Just go find those spots and stack up a snowman base. I'll do the decorating.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find those spots I marked out for the snowmen? I can't decorate until you've stacked the snowmen.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Really, you finished? Wow, you're fast! I'll head out shortly and decorate them. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q061c">
	    	<NAME>Dress for Success</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hmm, I really need to finish dressing my snowmen. Maybe you'd like to help out? Sure you would, you're my best friend! And best friends always help each other!
Take these items and go find my undecorated snowmen. I know there's one in Darby Field so you could start there. You can dress the snowmen however you like. I'll catch up with you in a bit. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you decorated the snowmen yet? I'll be along shortly to help out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, you finished already? Thanks for helping out, you're a great friend!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
<!-- Tropical Break -->
	<QUEST ID="Q062a">
	    	<NAME>Colors of the Parrot</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi there! Have you ever seen a Parrot Feather? They are very pretty and colorful. I've been collecting them to use for crafts.
If you happen to come across any Parrot Feathers as you travel around Pandanda please pick them up and bring them to me. You'd be helping me out a lot and I'll be glad to pay you for them.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had any luck finding the Parrot Feathers? I won't be able to complete my crafts without them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! You're a great friend for getting these for me. 
Here's the coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062b">
	    	<NAME>Message in a Bottle</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, how's the fishing going? I've heard rumors of Pandas sending messages across the sea by stuffing  parchment into a bottle and letting the waves carry it across the ocean. Wouldn't that be something!
If you're ever over at Coconut Beach and find some Bottled Messages floating out in the water, bring them to me and I'll give you some coins in return.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found any Bottled Messages yet? Head over to Coconut Beach and walk along the water, I'm sure you'll find something!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well what do you know, looks like the rumors were true!
Thanks for your help, here's some coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062c">
	    	<NAME>Bury Me Treasure</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! You look like a Panda I can trust. I've got some treasure that I need buried for safe keeping. You up for some hard work? Of course you are. You do this for me and I'll make sure you get rewarded. 
I've marked out 5 locations across Pandanda where you should bury a treasure chest. 2 of them are at Coconut Beach. When you find an 'X' just dig a hole and drop in the treasure. But make sure no one's looking! Come back when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you buried that treasure yet? Make sure no one sees you. Kind of pointless to bury treasure if everyone knows where it is.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
All done eh? Great job! Here's some coins for your honesty.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062d">
	    	<NAME>Pen Pineapple Apple Pen</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey buddy! The weather is warm and we need a new, improved and fresh version of Pen the Pig.
Could you collect 5 pineapples, 5 apples and 5 old sets of Pen the Pig around mPandanda Land? Apples can be found in The Orchard, Pineapples in The Orchard and Harvest Grove and Pen the Pig - anywhere.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Old sets of Pen the Pig are everywhere, we just need 5 of them in order to make a new, fresh version of Pen the Pig!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ay, now let's pen these apples and pineapples. Here we go! A left pen, an apple, a pineapple, a right pen. A few more improvements and it'll be ready for use by all Pandas. Thanks for helping me!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062e">
	    	<NAME>Peachy Pineapple Milkshake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC01337</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC01337</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey Panda pal! The weather is hot, it's time to chill at the beach... And what's better than a fresh milkshake? So we'll need some water from Fishing Hole (don't worry, it's clean!), 3 peaches, 3 pineapples and a quart of cream. We'll be giving around free peachy pineapple milkshakes (that will be our new fresh invention)!
Farmer Dan offers quarts of cream, peaches and pineapples can be found in The Orchard. Don't forget to get some fresh water samples from Fishing Hole!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Get some water from Fishing Hole. It's clean, Steve inspected it!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Sips, gulps. Ahh... This is quite refreshening. This is an incredible milkshake. You're amazing, thanks for your help, Panda pal!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062f">
	    	<NAME>Pineapple Ice Cream</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! There are new summer flavors and seems like the favorite ice cream this season is the pineapple one. And, so, I'm out of ingredients! I'll need 5 pineapples which you can find in Harvest Grove or The Orchard and 3 quarts of cream, which you can buy from Farmer Dan.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Those Pandas really want the pineapple ice cream! Have you collected any of the ingredients I need yet?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ay, these will do just fine, enough for the day. I'll collect some more after work. Here you go, some coins for your good job.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062g">
	    	<NAME>Pineapple Furniture</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey pal! We'll need to prepare some pineapple furniture with real pineapples and some wood. Yes, they'll be both tasty and will smell amazing! So we'll need 5 pineapples from The Orchard or Harvest Grove and 3 pieces of fresh cut wood from Pawthorne Forest. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Well, 3 pieces of fresh cut wood isn't really enough but we can still try with that amount. I know they're hard to get, but just be patient.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well done! Let me try and see if this wood would to the trick... According to these calculations, it will. If it doesn't, when I'm free, I'll go for more wood. Thanks, here's something for your hard work!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
<!-- Friendship Festival -->
	<QUEST ID="Q063a">
	    	<NAME>Cupcakes for My Friends</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Isn't the Friendship Festival wonderful? It's a great time to let your friends know how special they are to you. I made cupcakes for my friends but haven't been able to deliver all of them.
Would you do me a favor and hand out these cupcakes to Farmer Dan, Mr. Elmhurst, Tammy, Lisa, Jim, and Farmer Ned? Come see me when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you gotten a chance to deliver the cupcakes to my remaining friends? I don't want them to feel left out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! Friends like you are what make the Friendship Festival so great!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q063b">
	    	<NAME>A Gift for Izzy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, I was wondering if you could do a favor for me seeing as how we're such good friends. You know Izzy over at the Pet Shop, right? Well, I'd like to get her something special to celebrate the festival. 
There's a rare fish called the Majestic Angelfish that I know she'd really like. You can probably catch one over at Coconut Beach. Thanks!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you catch the Majestic Angelfish yet? I know Izzy will really like it. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What a nice surprise! I've been wanting a Majestic Angelfish for a while now. Joe is so thoughtful!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q063c">
	    	<NAME>Gifts for Joe</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi, would you have time to help me with something? I have a Fishing Guide book for Joe but left it in the Parlour at the House on Misty Hill. 
Could you retrieve the book and pick up a Box of Chocolates then deliver them to Joe at the Fishing Hole for me? You can purchase the Box of Chocolates from Mr. Elmhurst on West Market Street. You're a true friend!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to find the Fishing Guide book at the House on Misty Hill? Don't forget to stop by Mr. Elmhurst to purchase a Box of Chocolates for Joe.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What's this? A Fishing Guide and a Box of Chocolates? Wow, Izzy sure is nice!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q063d">
	    	<NAME>Donut Delivery</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! I do hope you are enjoying the Friendship Festival. Might I ask a favor? I've got some delicious donuts that I'd like to distribute to my friends. 
Would you mind handing them out to Paige at Bear Hollow, Lisa at Shady Glen, Tammy on East Market St., Mr. McWiggles at the Ice Cream Parlor, Farmer Ned at Harvest Grove, and Questy Greybeard at the Tree House Lobby? Return to me afterwards to collect your reward.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had the opportunity to deliver my donuts yet? I do hope you can hand them out before they get stale.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Splendid! Here's some coins for your generosity and assistance.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q064a">
	    	<NAME>Chocolate and Roses</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
How are you enjoying the Friendship Festival? Speaking of friendships, would you be able to help me out with something? I'd like to get a gift for Paige in Bear Hollow. 
Could you collect 5 Red Roses from Darby Field and deliver them with a Box of Chocolates to Paige for me? You can purchase a Box of Chocolates from Mr. Elmhurst on West Market Street. You'd be a real pal!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to find the Red Roses and get the Box of Chocolates? I sure hope Paige likes them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! These are from Jim? He's a really nice Panda.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q064b">
	    	<NAME>Lost Cards</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh no, I need your help! I've lost a whole batch of Valentine Cards! I worked so hard on them and now they're gone! The must have fallen out of my bag. 
Could you go and look for them for me? You're such a good friend, I'm sure you could find them if you tried.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find my Valentine Cards yet? I worked so hard on them. I really hope they arent lost forever.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You found them! I knew you could do it! Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q064c">
	    	<NAME>Be My Valentine</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Would you do me a favor since it's the Friendship Festival and you're such a good friend? I wrote a bunch of Valentine Cards and it'd be awesome if you could deliver them for me!
Let's see, I have one for Joe at the Fishing Hole, Steve on East Market Street, Jim on West Market Street, Fitch at Clothing Co., Paige in Bear Hollow, and Izzy in the Pet Shop. Let me know when you've handed them all out.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you delivered my Valentine Cards yet? I don't want people to think I forgot about them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Did you finish? Thanks! I'm so glad we're friends!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
<!-- Easter Festival -->
	<QUEST ID="Q040a">
	    	<NAME>Oh My, the Hens!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC014</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC014</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy, how's it been going for you recently? Is the egg hunt going well for you? I, personally, can say that an egg is a rare claim for some Pandas. I believe that it's because the brown chicken, which are not inside the barn, are losing feather. The white hens don't give a lot of eggs, though. Could you please get some eggs from the white chicken in my barn in order to get some eggs for the Pandas and find some feather that my brown chicken have lost?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I need you to find the feather that's fallen off my brown chicken, it's perhaps happening because they don't live in the barn. And, speaking of my barn, please visit the white hens in there in order to get some eggs for coloring.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Great, those eggs are enough for now. I'll use the feather for something. Thanks for your hard work.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040b">
	    	<NAME>Worms for Cute Chicks</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! As you may know it's the Easter Festival, there are egg hunts organized daily and it's huge. But let's not forget the cute little yellow chicks we've got over here! I want to give them a special snack. As you may know, their favorite snack are the worms, so I'd need some.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Worms can be found in Pawthorne Forest, Darby Field and Shady Glen. Aww, I can't wait to feed those little cuties!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yey, now I can give this special snack to my little fellas. Thanks! Here are some coins for your job.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040c">
	    	<NAME>Flowers Like Chicks</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Sweet, you're here! As you probably know, I'm big fan of animals and flowers. And since it's Easter Festival, chicks are the loveliest animals these days! Their yellow color reminds me of daffodils. Could you pick up some daffodils for me from the Orchard, please?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I love chicks and daffodils. Could you please bring me some daffodils from the Orchard?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
They indeed make my day sunnier and remind me of chicks! Thank you!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040d">
	    	<NAME>Lost Easter Eggs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC01337</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC01337</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
It's that time of the year again, yes, Easter! No matter the religion, all Pandas on Pandanda Land enjoy collecting eggs. But, uh-oh, while Mr. Elmhurst and I were hiding all of them around the island, I lost a few (feelsbadman). We need your help to find them all, they may be everywhere and Easter Egg Hunts are in their season!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
We really need those eggs back for the Easter Egg Hunts that we all have organized!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You're a true friend! Easter is saved thanks to you! Here is a small reward for your well-done job.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040e">
	    	<NAME>No Candy for Lisa</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello. I enjoy taking part in the easter egg hunts. BUT! I'm very unlucky when it comes to finding eggs with candy in it. I'm really sad. Please, bring me some candy so I can feel better.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Please, help me out, brighten my day. Find and bring me some candy. It's unfair, the rest have found lots of eggs with candy inside and I haven't found any!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks for making my day! I feel better now. Here's something to show my appreciation. Once again, thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040f">
	    	<NAME>Colored Chicken Feather</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC014</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
G'day! I've seen some rainbow colored chicken, which is quite weird. I know that some chicken are painted in bright rainbow color but they never got out of handle. Find some feather from such chicken and give it to Farmer Ned.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found this weird chicken feather yet? I'm even afraid to ask Ned what those chicken have done to his crops...
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, some painted chicken feather! This is surely weird, those chicken usually stay around Harvest Grove. I'll go searching for them, thanks for informing me.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040g">
	    	<NAME>Easter Mood Flowers</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! What a sunny day over here in Pandanda Land! And all those egg hunters! I love flowers just like Tammy. Could you please get me some colorful flowers? I love making bouquets.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Flowers can be found in the most of the places where there is soil.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks, those flowers make an amazing bouquet! Here are some coins.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q040h">
	    	<NAME>Bunnies and Eggs</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Good day! There are lots of bunnies during this time of the year, aren't there? Well, bunnies and colorful eggs go together. Could you find three Easter bunnies and three colorful eggs in Pandanda Land?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Bunnies can be found around Darby Field and Harvest Grove and eggs appear to be everywhere, haha.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Seems like you found the bunnies and the eggs! Here is your prize.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Intro -->
	<QUEST ID="Q101">
	    	<NAME>Quest Tutorial</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I see you noticed the yellow 'Q' above my head. That indicates I have a quest for you. If you accept it, then it will be listed in your Quest Log. You can open your Quest Log by clicking the yellow Q on your menu bar. There you can see the details, requirements, and status of your quests.
If you're ready for a quest, I could use your help. I was reading in the Book Nook and forgot my book there. Would you mind picking it up and bringing it to me?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Were you able to find my book? I think it had a brown cover.
You can enter the Book Nook up the steps to my left.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you for getting my book for me!
As you travel around Pandanda Land, you will find other Pandas that have Quests and need your help. Good luck!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- L50 -->
	<QUEST ID="Q110a">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 1)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC018</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Welcome! I see you have reached Level 50! That is no small accomplishment! I believe you have earned the right to learn the art of dragon taming. It is not an easy task but the reward is well worth the effort!
I would ask that you first speak with Trixie in Pawthorne Forest. She is very wise in the ways of dragons. Here, take this letter to her and she will guide you further.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>You will most likely find Trixie in Pawthorne Forest. Go there at once and show her the letter I gave you.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hmm, Questy believes you are ready to tame your own dragon! I'm not so sure but I will defer to his judgment and help you nonetheless. 
The first thing you will need is a collection of rare gems. Take this list to Jim on West Market Street and he will explain how best to gather these rare gems.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110b">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 2)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hmm, Questy believes you are ready to tame your own dragon! I'm not so sure, but I will defer to his judgment and help you nonetheless. 
The first thing you will need is a collection of rare gems. Take this list to Jim on West Market Street and he will explain how best to gather these rare gems.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the list of rare gems to Jim on West Market Street. He can help you.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, this is quite the list! This wouldn't have anything to do with dragons would it? Not really any of my business I suppose.  
These gems can all be found in Pandanda Land, but won't be found easily. You've gathered gems for me before so just go out and do your best. Come back when you've got them all.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110c">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 3)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, this is quite the list! This wouldn't have anything to do with dragons would it? Not really any of my business I suppose.  
These gems can all be found in Pandanda Land, but won't be found easily. You've gathered gems for me before so just go out and do your best. Come back when you've got them all.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Have you found the gems yet? They could be anywhere around Pandanda Land.  Well, except not indoors of course.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well look at that! These are beautiful. I'll get these polished up for you but you'll need a chest to carry them all in.
Take this blueprint over to Steve on East Market Street. He should be able to build a nice sturdy chest for you. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110d">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 4)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Well look at that! These are beautiful. I'll get these polished up for you but you'll need a chest to carry them all in.
Take this blueprint over to Steve on East Market Street. He should be able to build a nice sturdy chest for you. 
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>While I polish these gems up, head over to Steve on East Market Street to see about that chest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What's this? You're in need of a chest eh? Well I could build one for you but I'll need some wood first. 
Head over to Pawthorne Forest and gather up some fresh cut wood and I'll be able to complete your chest.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110e">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 5)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What's this? You're in need of a chest eh? Well I could build one for you but I'll need some wood first. 
Head over to Pawthorne Forest and gather up some fresh cut wood and I'll be able to complete your chest.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Did you get that wood from Pawthorne Forest yet? Can't make a chest without wood.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
So, you've returned with the wood? I've just completed your chest as specified by the blueprints you gave me. It's very sturdy and should hold whatever you need it to.
I suppose you should head back to Jim now to fill it up! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110f">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 6)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
So, you've returned with the wood? I've just completed your chest as specified by the blueprints you gave me. It's very sturdy and should hold whatever you need it to.
I suppose you should head back to Jim now to fill it up! 
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>That's one of the best chests I've ever crafted. Head over to Jim to fill it up.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hello again. I see you've got the chest built. I'm done polishing the gems so let's load them into the chest and see if it holds together. 
There you go. Take the chest and gems back to Trixie and good luck!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110g">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 7)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello again. I see you've got the chest built. I'm done polishing the gems so let's load them into the chest and see if it holds together. 
There you go. Take the chest and gems back to Trixie and good luck!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the chest and gems back to Trixie. You'll probably find her in Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You have returned with the gems! Excellent work! They will be very useful later on. However, more items are needed before you will be ready to tame a full grown dragon.
The next thing you must do is prepare a large feast. Take this list to Fishy Joe and he will help you prepare it.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110h">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 8)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You have returned with the gems! Excellent work! They will be very useful later on. However, more items are needed before you will be ready to tame a full grown dragon.
The next thing you must do is prepare a large feast. Take this list to Fishy Joe and he will help you prepare it.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the list to Fishy Joe at the Fishing Hole, he will help you make a feast fit for a dragon.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hey there. So you need help making a large feast for a dragon? Sounds dangerous but I'll help you out. Let's see. 
You'll need 3 Large Salmon, 2 Large Trout, and 2 Large Catfish. The trout and catfish can be found here but the best salmon are caught on Coconut Beach. Come back and see me when you're done.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110i">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 9)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there. So you need help making a large feast for a dragon? Sounds dangerous but I'll help you out. Let's see. 
You'll need 3 Large Salmon, 2 Large Trout, and 2 Large Catfish. The trout and catfish can be found here but the best salmon are caught on Coconut Beach. Come back and see me when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Go catch those fish and I'll prepare the other items for the large feast.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You caught them all? Great! Let me just clean them here and add them to this arrangement. I hope this is satisfactory. Dragons can be very picky when it comes to food.
They are all done. Take this back to Trixie as quickly as you can. I'd hate for a dragon to catch you with it before you're fully prepared.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110j">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 10)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You caught them all? Great! Let me just clean them here and add them to this arrangement. I hope this is satisfactory. Dragons can be very picky when it comes to food.
They are all done. Take this back to Trixie as quickly as you can. I'd hate for a dragon to catch you with it before you're fully prepared.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Be careful carrying that feast around. You don't want a dragon to swoop down and take you away with it.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You are making good progress. The chest full of rare gems and the large feast are all prepared. 
The last thing you'll need is a Beacon Staff which will summon a dragon. Questy Greybeard will have a Beacon Staff for you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110k">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 11)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC018</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You are making good progress. The chest full of rare gems and the large feast are all prepared. 
The last thing you'll need is a Beacon Staff which will summon a dragon. Questy Greybeard will have a Beacon Staff for you. Take this letter to Questy detailing your progress.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the letter to Questy and he will provide you with a Beacon Staff.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, young Panda, I see you have prepared yourself for the dragon summoning under Trixie's tutelage. Here, take this Beacon Staff and return to Trixie once more. She will give you final instructions on summoning a dragon. 
I know when the time comes, you will be brave, and honor all the Pandas that have come before you who have had the courage to bond with the dragon kin.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110l">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 12)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC018</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, young Panda, I see you have prepared yourself for the dragon summoning under Trixie's tutelage. Here, take this Beacon Staff and return to Trixie once more. She will give you final instructions on summoning a dragon. 
I know when the time comes, you will be brave, and honor all the Pandas that have come before you who have had the courage to bond with the dragon kin.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Return to Trixie with the Beacon Staff and prepare yourself for the summoning!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You are nearly ready. But first I must imbue this Beacon Staff to summon either a Blue Dragon or a Grey Dragon. You may only summon one or the other, not both. Choose wisely!
When you have decided which dragon you wish to summon, speak with me again. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<QUEST ID="Q111">
	    	<NAME>Summon a Grey Dragon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC022</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
The time has come to summon a dragon. I will imbue the beacon staff to call forth a Grey Dragon.  If you wish to summon a Blue Dragon instead, do not accept this quest.
You must take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach. There you will find a marking in the sand. Place these items and hopefully a dragon will come and decide not to eat you. Good luck!		
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach and place them on the marking in the sand.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Who is it that summons me? You seek to buy my loyalty with these gifts? It is a brave Panda that dares to tempt a dragon! 
However, you must know something of dragon lore to provide such gifts and I sense  your heart is pure. Yes, you are a special Panda. Come, you may ride on my back and we will have many adventures together!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<QUEST ID="Q112">
	    	<NAME>Summon a Blue Dragon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC022</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
The time has come to summon a dragon. I will imbue the beacon staff to call forth a Blue Dragon.  If you wish to summon a Grey Dragon instead, do not accept this quest.
You must take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach. There you will find a marking in the sand. Place these items and hopefully a dragon will come and decide not to eat you. Good luck!		
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach and place them on the marking in the sand.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Who is it that summons me? You seek to buy my loyalty with these gifts? It is a brave Panda that dares to tempt a dragon! 
However, you must know something of dragon lore to provide such gifts and I sense  your heart is pure. Yes, you are a special Panda. Come, you may ride on my back and we will have many adventures together!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Stranger -->
	<QUEST ID="Q113">
	    	<NAME>The New Journey Begins</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC027</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC028</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello there. You seem interested in who I am. For you, I'm a complete stranger. This might change, though.
It's time for the new journey and a riddle: "An underground tunnel to outside passes under a tree". Take it, if you wish and dare. If you need help later, visit my friend Jim.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
An underground tunnel to outside passes under a tree.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well done, you have found the secret underground tunnel. You just took the key for it, you can use it whenever to reach this place.
I'll go away now the same way I appeared.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Lily -->
	<QUEST ID="Q1337a">
	    <NAME>A New Journey Begins</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
A new journey begins in mPandanda!! Quests are RIGHT OVER HERE!!!! I'm so hyped! But we don't know a lot about them. You have to find the old Pandanda books which are lost by McWiggles and Paige around the island so that we can continue with quests further.
Do you accept the challenge, Panda?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found the three books? I heard that one of them is in The Den.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
AWESOME! You have collected them all! It'll take us a few days to prepare the tasks for you as McWiggles and I will be going through all of the books! 
As it's the beginning of the journey, I'll give you some extra panda power so you can level up. Can't wait to give you quests!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Questy -->
	<QUEST ID="Q018a">
	    <NAME>Burning Fever Like Never</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Cough, cough! Ah, here you are! I've been waiting for you. I really need your help as I've been sick lately... and I have never experienced such a sickness! As far as I remember, this one is called Daffodil Fever, from which pandas have the feeling that they're burning in lava. Collect 3 gold mushrooms from Pawthorne Forest, Bunny Field and Fishing Hole for the cure, please.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found some gold mushrooms yet? I know they can be seen in Pawthorne Forest, Bunny Field and Fishing Hole if you look for them more thoroughly.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Oh, this fever! I'm so hot and I feel like I'm burning in lava that I forgot to tell you that the gold mushrooms aren't the only ingredient for the cure but again, I forgot what the rest are. Head over to Lisa, she remembers the rest. Hurry up please, the feeling is awful!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q018b">
	    <NAME>Burning Fever Like Never</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Oh, you're finally here! Questy Greybeard told me about his awful fever and that you're up with the task to find the rest of the ingredients for the cure. Let's see, as far as I remember, you need four cherries, a lump of coal and a very special ingredient that only William McWiggles owns - a cola ice cream.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Look for those ingredients more carefully, I'm sure you'll find them. Make sure you buy the cola ice cream from the Buy Items section at McWiggles!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Aw, you got the ingredients, yay! Hurry up and give the potion I just gave you to Questy, hopefully he gets better soon.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q018c">
	    <NAME>Burning Fever Like Never</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there, I see you have got the cure! Thanks a lot! Could you please give it to me?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Please, give me the potion so I can feel better.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you very much! You're an awesome, outgoing and helpful Panda! The potion will make me feel better and soon I'll be able to give Quest Rewards again, full of cheer. As a thank-you, please, accept these coins and Panda Power and thank Lisa for me.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<!-- Q018 CANT BE USED ANYMORE -->
	<QUEST ID="Q019a">
	    <NAME>A Magical Potion</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Good day, fellow Panda magician. As you know, I'm the island's magician and I create lots of different potions and cures. The potion that I decided to make is quite interesting, though, its effect will remain a secret for now. So, I'll need 2 Ghoul Eyes from Misty Hill or Pawthorne Forest, 4 Bat Wings from East Market Street and some indoor locations. I also need you to prepare all the cauldrons from 5 different locations.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you collected all the ingredients for the potion yet?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Those ingredients are enough to make my magical potion. Thank you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019b">
	    <NAME>Orange Tasting Potion</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Howdy! How's your day going so far? I'm making the so-called Orange Potion today. The ingredients, you're asking. I need 2 Spiders from Pawthorne Forest, 3 Oranges from The Orchard and a Snizzle Fizzle potion from Paige.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
The potion I'm creating may sound weird but it's quite useful, if you pour it into a pot with soil, oranges will directly appear.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
It's time to grow those oranges, thanks for helping me out.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019c">
	    <NAME>Magical Book Creation</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello! There are quite interesting magical books, possessing powers you haven't even imagined... They're amazing! I'm going to create one today. In order to do so, I'll need the book "A History of Dragons", which can be found somewhere indoors, some glue, some old newspapers and a Haunted Potion.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm pretty sure that you can find the stuff I need.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Here we go, this is the magical book on how to summon a dragon... I'll pass a copy of it to you later.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019d">
	    <NAME>A Potion Mix</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! How's it going so far for you? What potions have you used recently? Speaking of potions, we're going to mix some. I'm going to mix some Turbo Potion, Dragon Tears Potion and Ghost Leaf Potion in the Cauldrons on the Misty Hill and in the Barn. Could you collect this all?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm pretty sure that you can buy the potions from Paige... Be careful, there are 2 of each kind which look exactly the same and one of them is the one I need.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done, amazing job! Let's see what this mix will do.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019e">
	    <NAME>The Poisonous Mushrooms</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there Panda, I need your help! Tonight, Izzy will be cooking her famous mushroom soup to be served on the Community Center's feast. However, in my daily walk around, I stumbled upon some seemingly edible mushrooms growing in the fields, that were in fact some of the most poisonous species ever found around these lands. A less experienced panda, like Izzy, may collect those by mistake, turning the delicious dinner into a hazard to all Pandas. Could you help me and collect them before Izzy does?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Check out the pictures I gave you as objectives, they'll help you identify the mushrooms.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Yay, you found them, you have a good eye Panda! I'm glad you learned a lesson with ol' Questy. It's really important to distinguish edible mushroom species from poisonous ones, as the last ones are toxic and are very dangerous for our bodies. However, that is no easy task! Some of them are really easy to differentiate, but others are very identical to the ones we can eat. You should always get advice from an experienced mushroom collector, as they know the guidelines to safely pick those delicious mushrooms! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019f">
	    <NAME>Zing's Tent</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello fellow magician! Apart from the magical stuff I do, I have to do some regular work. Today, I'll be fixing some holes in Zing's tent - I need to be patching them. Could you help me out? I'll need a few Spools of Thread - you can find some that other Pandas have lost and a Needle from Paige.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I need to patch Zing's tent here and there and I'm glad you're going to help me.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks! Now I can start patching his tent. I'll do my best to make it look as good as new!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019g">
	    <NAME>A Love-ly Potion</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! Do you feel the love? Yeah, love is in the air! And Lisa asked me to help her again. She's really in love with Jasper, the ghost that lives in Haunted Hallway, as you probably know. We've tried different potions to stop other ghosts from trying to keep them away from each other and they have failed for the most part. Today, we'll be transforming Lisa into a Panda Ghost - we'll need 5 Ghostflowers and some Moon Sand from Misty Hill, 4 Angry Ghosts that can be found somewhere around mPandanda Land and Spices from Farmer Ned - some magic later as well.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
That potion is going to be extremely complicated - hopefully you'll manage to find the ingredients.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks for the potion ingredients and now it's time for the special magic spell. Seviyorum seni, s'agapo poli. Yo te quiero a ti, volim te, mon cheri. Mangava tut mange, voglio bene a te. Men seni sevirem, ya habibi, je t'aime. Love unlimited!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019h">
	    <NAME>Flint Nibbles Magic</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Howdy! Would you like to make some little cute dragons happy? Surely you do! Today I'll be making some Flint Nibbles. You're wondering perhaps, how are they made so that they can give the little dragons the ability to breathe fire? You'll get to know now! First, we'll need some regular Potatoes from Harvest Grove as well as some Chili Peppers. Then, I'll cast the magic spell that will make them get combined into those magical little tasty fireballs.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Yes, making Flint Nibbles involves magic, haha.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Now that we've got the Potatoes and the Chili Peppers, it's time to cast the magic spell. Potate, patato, patati, flint nibbles-ey!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019i">
	    <NAME>Dragon Potion</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello! Do you know Paige's potions catalog in Bear Hollow? Yep, that's right! Today I'll be making a few potions because they're out of stock. You need to find two small dragons, some Moon Sand and two rare giant gems from Pawthorne Forest and Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
No, the little dragons are not used in the dragon potion - we need them in order to start the magical process.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Poof! Thanks for the potion! I'll now be taking those little cuties back to the Pet Shop. Did you really think they are an ingredient?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019j">
	    <NAME>Companionship</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Good evening Panda! I hope you and your dragons are getting along just fine. While you are here, do you think you could do me a quick favor? I will give you a nice reward if you choose to accept! I'm helping Trixie with teaching other Pandas how to tame dragons and we've had our hands full all day. Could you visit Coconut Beach and fish 5 Large Salmons for me? The dragons are getting a little impatient and we will have to feed them soon. We don't want them to eat anybody! Return to me once you have caught the Salmon. I need help with something else as well!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Just make sure to come back after you have caught the Large Salmon.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Ah, you've arrived just in the nick of time! Thank you for bringing me the salmon! I am confident that you too will one day become a master at teaching others how to tame their own dragon. I have one last favor to ask you for. Please visit Maggie in the Barn and deliver this scroll to her! It should help her stop her pony from escaping again. I told her I would give it to her this morning but I wasn't able to. Thank you and let me know once you deliver the scroll!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019k">
	    <NAME>Companionship</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC024</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Ah, you've arrived just in the nick of time! Thank you for bringing me the salmon! I am confident that you too will one day become a master at teaching others how to tame their own dragon. I have one last favor to ask you for. Please visit Maggie in the Barn and deliver this scroll to her! It should help her stop her pony from escaping again. I told her I would give it to her this morning but I wasn't able to. Thank you and let me know once you deliver the scroll!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I'd be very pleased if you could give Maggie the scroll.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Wow, I wasn't expecting to receive this today. I was starting to lose hope! Thank you for the scroll! You don't know how much trouble this pony has been causing recently. Please let Questy know I said thank you!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019l">
	    <NAME>Companionship</NAME>
	    <START>NPC024</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Wow, I wasn't expecting to receive this today. I was starting to lose hope! Thank you for the scroll! You don't know how much trouble this pony has been causing recently. Please let Questy know I said thank you!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Tell Questy thank-you from me!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you so much for your efforts, time and hard work! I wouldn't have had the time to do these myself. Pleace accept this as a token of my gratitude.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q019m">
	    <NAME>The Magic of the Rose</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello fellow Panda pal! Have you heard about unleashing the true power of the Rose? It's basically all about making it magical. How is this done, you would probably ask. Well, we'll need 5 Roses from Darby Field and 5 Ghostflowers from Misty Hill first.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Unleashing the magical power of the Rose is going to do amazing things!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Now these magic Roses can cast a love spell and make their holder fall in love with someone! Oh, this is so romantic!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Mr. Elmhurst -->
	<QUEST ID="Q010a">
	    <NAME>Build Furniture Project</NAME>
	    <START>NPC009</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC009</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Good day, Panda! As you may know, I'm the one who sells furniture to mPandanda citizens which of the highest quality and it's made by me. Though, recently, I've had a shortage of materials for some wooden furniture like nails and wood itself. Could you please collect some for me? I'm pretty sure Maggie has some nails and wood can be found in Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found some wood yet? You can find some in Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Good you found those! I'll also need some glue because nails can't be used for everything, you know. Could you please visit Steve in East Market Street? He should know where you can find some glue.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q010b">
	    <NAME>Build Furniture Project</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC009</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey, I heard that Mr. Elmhurst needs some glue for his handmade furniture. Sure, I remember I saw a shiny, new tube of glue somewhere indoors. Give it to Mr. Elmhurst when you find it.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Hey, I heard that Mr. Elmhurst needs some glue for his handmade furniture. Sure, I remember I saw a shiny, new tube of glue somewhere indoors. Give it to Mr. Elmhurst when you find it.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks a lot for the materials! You really did a great job. Here's a thing I put up real quick, hope you like it.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!--Lily, Paige and Ned-->
	<QUEST ID="Q031a">
	    <NAME>It Stings Like Jellyfish</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Howdy fellow! I know it's mostly Steve's and Joe's job, but a few Pandas have just told me that the whole coast of Coconut Beach is full of... jellyfish! Some have even been stung by a jellyfish and I have asked Questy to help me. We need quick reactions. Fast, please, get to the beach and catch all the jellyfish! Make sure to catch them carefully and don't touch their tentacles in any way.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Catch all the jellyfish from Coconut Beach before they sting other Pandas. Make sure to catch them carefully and don't touch their tentacles in any way!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Phew, that was close. Now, perhaps, I'll bring them to Izzy to make a soup or to Questy for some spell.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031b">
	    <NAME>Paint Leaks</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
I'm so worried, I have just received an urgent mail from our Paint Factory on the Faraway Lands: "Dear Lily, I'm afraid that the dragon responsible for transporting our ink buckets had an accident on his way to mPandanda, letting them spill over the ocean. Soon enough, those buckets will reach your lands and will leak. You must find them before that happens!". Oh no, we must hurry! If that paint spreads to the shore, it will damage all the water sources on our land, it would be chaos! Please, I'll need your help to find those buckets in time!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You have to fish up all the buckets from all the shores around Pandanda Land.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you, we all owe you a lot for your actions! Now we should get our water analyzed so that we are sure that it is safe for drinking, fishing and swimming. Please talk to Steve, he's getting the water analysis kit ready for use. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031c">
	    <NAME>Paint Leaks</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Here is the water analysis kit, make sure you follow the instructions! You need 5 water samples, one from each water mass on our land, in order to get accurate results. Good luck!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Here is the water analysis kit, make sure you follow the instructions! You need 5 water samples, one from each water mass on our land, in order to get accurate results. Good luck!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
That's it...let's check it out... in conclusion, everything is fine! That was close! All the water remains safe for the mPandanda Community usage. Thank you!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031d">
	    <NAME>Ghost Leaf Potions</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Psst... Panda... Come here. Don't tell anyone, but my stock of Ghost Leaf Potions is running low and I forgot to order new supplies this week! Can you help me find the ingredients around mPandanda Land, so that I can make some new potions? Let me see, I will need a few Ghost Flowers and an Angry Ghost (exclusive from Misty Hill) to extract its magic, a couple Purple Mushrooms... oh, and a Raspberry, for that delicious flavour! 
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
How's ingredients collecting going? Have you found the enough amount of Ghost Flowers and Purple Mushrooms, an Angry Ghost and a Raspberry?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thank you Panda, I knew I could count on you. Let me prepare the potion and you can take some of it with you. It will be our little secret... 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031e">
	    <NAME>Crow Attacks</NAME>
	    <START>NPC014</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC014</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey pal! My dear scarecrow, Mr. Fiddles, is being attacked by crows once again. Those merciless birds... they keep hurting my friend and he doesn't seem to scare them! Please, can you bring me some items in order to repair Mr. Fiddles? I need to scare those evil birds! I will need some coal from Pawthorne Forest, some hay you can find around and a farmer costume from Fitch in Clothing Co.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I'll need some coal from Pawthorne Forest, you can go around and look for hay and buy a farmer costume from Fitch.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
I hope those birds dont come back! Thank you my friend. Now I should fix my Fiddly.  Here is a little reward for you. Come check him out later!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031f">
	    <NAME>Lost in Translation</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day fellow! Have you heard the news? Sheriff went nuts! A bunch of naughty Pandas from the Faraway Lands have come recently to mPandanda Land, causing all sort of trouble! Now, they are dodging Sheriffs speech rules, saying bad words in their foreign language. When Sheriff went to the Book Nook in order to get a dictionary, he noticed that all the pages have been ripped off! An hour ago, Questy reported finding a bunch of pages flying around. They will eventually land somewhere! All of us are trying to help Sheriff and find the pages, will you join?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Just remember, those pages can appear everywhere. Just wait and be patient and you'll see some, the wind can't take them too far!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks, I think that we'll be able to get the pages together now. Sheriff told me to warn everybody to report all bad Pandas! Here is a reward for helping us and being a good Panda.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031g">
	    <NAME>Potion Passion</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Hey there Panda! Trixie wants me to teach her how to make potions and I'll need some ingredients. I can't leave my spot here, Pandas buy lots of potions these days. Can you bring me a Sugar Beet from The Orchard, 3 Moonstones from Pawthorne Forest and 2 Azurites from Shady Glen?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Don't worry, I'll pay you well later. I hope that 90 coins are enough.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thank you very much, you've saved me a lot of time! Here are the coins I promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031h">
	    <NAME>Sewing Attempts</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I've decided to give sewing a try. I'm not really certain where I could start and Lily would be helping me as well, but I was wondering, where could I find some materials like buttons and thread? Could you bring me some? I have ordered a box of buttons and a spool of thread but they seem to have been lost around mPandanda Land. They should be somewhere indoors for sure, you can't leave threads outdoors.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
The thread and the buttons should be somewhere indoors.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Yay, you found some of those, now I can start! I'll hop over to Lily's, she's going to teach me how to sew. Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031i">
	    <NAME>Toys for Kids</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
G'day pal! I love showing charity to kids and so I decided to make some toys for the pookie Pandas around. I'll need a box of nails as well as a tube of glue from indoors, plus some wood from Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Showing charity is such a good thing! I believe that everybody should do a small good deed every day.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the materials! Now I can make the little pookies happy.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031j">
	    <NAME>Pumpkin Carving</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Hi! Pumpkin carving is not only done during Pumpkin Festival, I believe that it could be done throughout the whole year. I'm going to teach the kids how to make a beatiful pumpkin carving. It's all about their imagination and the right tools! However, I don't have enough pumpkins for all the kids. Could you bring me some more from Harvest Grove or Shady Glen?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You can find good pumpkins in Harvest Grove and Shady Glen.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Oh, you are such a sweetheart! The kids won't forget what you did for them! You can stop by later and do some pumpkin carving with them.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031k">
	    <NAME>Chilling by the Fire</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC010</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Yo Panda! I am planning a small party at Coconut Beach tonight by the campfire so that we can have fun together! Can you deliver those invitations instead of me? There's one for each of the Pandas like Paige, Izzy and so on. After you're done, could you visit Farmer Dan and see how his task to get the fire ready is going?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I really hope that my friends will enjoy that small party of mine!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thank god you're here! The good ol' Questy can't cast his fire spell because the wood there is all gone. Could you find some wood and coal so that we can build a fire? I'll be looking for some too.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031l">
	    <NAME>Chilling by the Fire</NAME>
	    <START>NPC010</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC010</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Thank god you're here! The good ol' Questy can't cast his fire spell because the wood there is all gone. Could you find some wood and coal so that we can build a fire? I'll be looking for some too.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Thank god you're here! The good ol' Questy can't cast his fire spell because the wood there is all gone. Could you find some wood and coal so that we can build a fire? I'll be looking for some too.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
We are a good team Panda! Let's get back to the party, everyone is waiting for us! Oh, and I found these coins in the dirt while I was collecting wood - they're yours now.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031m">
	    <NAME>Planting is Important</NAME>
	    <START>NPC024</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC014</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Hello and g'day fellow farmer! As you probably know, so many Pandas come here in Harvest Grove to pick up different berries. However, Farmer Ned and I can't just keep up with the quantity that's picked up and we need some help with planting raspberries, strawberries and blueberries. Will you help?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
We need to plant all those berries in Harvest Grove and I'm glad that you will be helping out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the help - I really don't have the time to plant that many berry plants that often.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031n">
	    <NAME>Planting in Pots</NAME>
	    <START>NPC014</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Howdy fella! How's it going? We've got a lot of gardening and planting going on here, so you can join in if you want. Actually, we'll be making some pots for planting. Will you take this blueprint to William McWiggles? I've heard he's got some great new pots.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I suppose McWiggles has made the pots on his own.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Hmm, this blueprint seems interesting. However, I haven't made the pots myself - Steve helped me. Head over to him, he may help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031o">
	    <NAME>Planting in Pots</NAME>
	    <START>NPC001</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Hmm, this blueprint seems interesting. However, I haven't made the pots myself - Steve helped me. Head over to him, he may help.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You need to talk to Steve, I can't make pots on my own.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Okay, I will help you and Farmer Ned with the pots - I'll need some wood and glue.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031p">
	    <NAME>Planting in Pots</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Okay, I will help you and Farmer Ned with the pots - I'll need some wood and glue.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Bring me some wood and glue and I'll be glad to help out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Thanks for the materials, I'm starting work right away! I'll give Farmer Ned the pots later.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031q">
	    <NAME>Learning to Fish</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Hey my fellow friend! What's up? I've asked Joe today how to fish and he told me that all I need is a lost fishing guidebook, a fishing pole and a net that somebody could have forgotten in Coconut Beach. Will you bring me those?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I really want to try fishing, I'm so excited!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Oh my god, thank you very much! Will you join and show me some techniques later? I've heard that you're very experienced in fishing!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031r">
	    <NAME>Orange Roses</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! Have you heard of Orange Roses? They're extremely rare and today I will be trying to create one. For this very specific purpose, I'll need 3 Oranges from The Orchard, 3 Pumpkins from Harvest Grove and 3 Roses from Darby Field. Could you help?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
The orange rose is a very specific type of rose.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Well done! Now I can start creating the special rose. Thank you!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q031s">
	    <NAME>Fashion Show</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Hey hey hey! How are you doing fella? Will you be joining Panda's special Fashion Show tonight? I surely will! I'll be making an interesting outfit but I'm not sure how I will combine it all. Oh, by the way, I can't find anywhere the items I need - will you help me and find them? I'll need a Pirate Hat, a pair of Glasses, a pair of Overalls and a pair of Bunny Slippers. May sound a weird combination but everybody will be amazed, I believe!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Weird outfits are my reserved rights. All rights reserved by Lily from mPandanda, haha!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
		<TEXTEND>
Oh, sweet, you have found all the clothing items I need, thank you so much! Tonight is my time to shine!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	
	<!-- Moon Festival Party Plot -->
	<QUEST ID="Q706a">
	    <NAME>Mysterious Occurrences</NAME>
	    <START>NPC029</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC029</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC007</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello there. I see that you're wondering who I am... Well I'm just another random mysterious guy on mPandanda. Like, this isn't new to the Pandanda Land citizens as if this is something regular. Anyhow, I can share a secret with you. I found some interesting objects and sand that had fallen from them in Shady Glen.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You can try collecting some sand in Shady Glen and bringing it to Jim.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Oh, interesting! Moon sand! I will analyze it. However, I need a special substance to experiment with it. Visit Questy and I'm sure he'll tell you a way to prepare it.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q706b">
	    <NAME>Mysterious Occurrences</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
All right, I see that you need a special liquid for experiments with moon sand. I can't make it, but I'll tell you the recipe and after you're ready with collecting the needed I'll tell you who can make one. So, let's see... We'll need three lumps of coal, some water and 4 coconuts, which we'll chop later.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
All right, I see that you need a special liquid for experiments with moon sand. I can't make it, but I'll tell you the recipe and after you're ready with collecting the needed I'll tell you who can make one. So, let's see... We'll need three lumps of coal, some water and 4 coconuts, which we'll chop later.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
I see that you've got what you need. Hold on for a second, let me chop the coconuts into small pieces. I'll have to use some magic, so close your eyes!
There you go! Go to Paige and ask her to make the substance for you. Oh, and also tell her a hi from me!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q706c">
	    <NAME>Mysterious Occurrences</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
There you go! Go to Paige and ask her to make the substance for you. Oh, and also tell her a hi from me!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
There you go! Go to Paige and ask her to make the substance for you. Oh, and also tell her a hi from me!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Now you can go and give the potion to Jim! Good luck with figuring out this mystery!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q706d">
	    <NAME>Mysterious Occurrences</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC007</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Now you can go and give the potion to Jim! Good luck with figuring out this mystery!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Now you can go and give the potion to Jim! Good luck with figuring out this mystery!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Hmm, let's add it to the moon sand you gave me... and voila!
Seems like it has fallen off a unidetified flying object or an astronaut suit. Wait... You told me that a stranger has told you about these mysterious occurences. Perhaps it belongs to him or an astronaut... or an alien? You can try going around and finding the answer.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q706e">
	    <NAME>Mysterious Occurrences</NAME>
	    <START>NPC007</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC030</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC030</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Seems like it has fallen off a unidetified flying object or an astronaut suit. Wait... You told me that a stranger has told you about these mysterious occurences. Perhaps it belongs to him or an astronaut... or an alien? You can try going around and finding the answer.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Seems like it has fallen off a unidetified flying object or an astronaut suit. Wait... You told me that a stranger has told you about these mysterious occurences. Perhaps it belongs to him or an astronaut... or an alien? You can try going around and finding the answer.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Hey, you found me! I'm an astronaut and I just came back from an outer space mission. Seems like there are aliens on the moon! They were kind enough to give me this flying saucer. Sadly, we cannot go back to the moon because they're too shy, but we can travel to outer space! See you later!
Oh, and don't forget to get an exclusive suit from me before leaving Shady Glen because it's super rare and perhaps we won't meet anytime soon again.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Moon Festival Party Plot Quest 2 -->
	
	<QUEST ID="Q201706a">
	    <NAME>UFO Sightnings</NAME>
	    <START>NPC009</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there! Have you seen the UFO in Shady Glen? It's very interesting! There are some interesting sounds there so I'd recommend you to check it Shady Glen out, record some sound and bring it to Steve for analysis - it's very interesting and mysterious!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Go to Shady Glen and record some of the sounds there, let's see what kind of aliens have given us this beautiful saucer!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
This sounds interesting. As you may know, I'm a sound expert and this does sound kinda... weird. I'm sure Paige would know something more about it, so talk to her!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201706b">
	    <NAME>UFO Sightnings</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
This sounds interesting. As you may know, I'm a sound expert and this does sound kinda... weird. I'm sure Paige would know something more about it, so talk to her!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
This sounds interesting. As you may know, I'm a sound expert and this does sound kinda... weird. I'm sure Paige would know something more about it, so talk to her!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
I know what this is. Nothing extraordinary. I'll give you a riddle and you need to solve it: "Only one other person besides me knows more about these sounds. He's hiding in a mysterious, cold, foggy and creepy place."
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201706c">
	    <NAME>UFO Sightnings</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC031</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
I know what this is. Nothing extraordinary. I'll give you a riddle and you need to solve it: "Only one other person besides me knows more about these sounds. He's hiding in a mysterious, cold, foggy and creepy place."
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I know what this is. Nothing extraordinary. I'll give you a riddle and you need to solve it: "Only one other person besides me knows more about these sounds. He's hiding in a mysterious, cold, foggy and creepy place."
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Yes, I do know what these sounds are from: aliens, which live on the moon! They were really kind and gave me some nice decorations - a clothes rack (you can put your astronaut suit on it!) and a small UFO for your treehouse. Take my items now because I'm going on a mission later!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Moon Fest Party Quests -->
	<QUEST ID="Q1706a">
	    <NAME>Moon Sandcastles</NAME>
	    <START>NPC004</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC004</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Oh hey! Have you recently heard about an UFO sightning and some moon sand around? It's super cool! I'm wondering, can we make sandcastles from this moon sand? There's only one way to find out. Could you please bring me 7 piles of moon sand? Thanks in advance!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Moon sandcastles sound interesting to make. Will 7 piles of moon sand be enough, or we'll need more? Hmmm... Nevermind, we can always find some more moon sand in Bear Hollow, Shady Glen or Misty Hill.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Now we just have to take it to Coconut Beach and find out if we need to add water to it or something else. Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1706b">
	    <NAME>Beautiful Souvenirs</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello fellow Panda pal! You seem to enjoy what's going on here a lot! So I suppose that you'll like my quest. I'd like to ask you to collect some Moon (also known as Ghost) flowers, some moonstone and some light opal gems with a beautiful moon color! These are beautiful souvenirs from this event, aren't they?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Opals and ghost flowers go very well together, they're awesome! You can find some of them in Misty Hill and Darby Field.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
These do look awesome! Thank you buddy!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1706c">
	    <NAME>Experimenting with Fruits</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! I have decided to experiment with fruits and find out how moon substances affect them. I'd like to ask you to bring me 2 apples, 2 cherries and some moon sand.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Apples and cherries are usually found on Orchard trees. Moon sand can be found near the UFO.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Now it's time to see how it works out! I hope the moon sand makes them taste even better. It is said to be good for planting because it contains a lot of minerals.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1706d">
	    <NAME>Blue Moon Ice Cream</NAME>
	    <START>NPC001</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Greetings! Perhaps you're here to check what ice cream flavors I've got. Well, I decided to add something interesting for the Moon Festival to match the taste of the Pandanda Land citizens these days - a Blue Moon flavor! Well, for it I'll need some ingredients - a sugar beet, 5 blueberries and some milk. Could you bring me these?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You can harvest blueberries in Harvest Grove and they'll make the ice cream look blue! Adding more milk and suger makes the color exactly the one we want.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Way to go! Now I've got what I need to make my new ice cream. Here's your reward.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1706e">
	    <NAME>Moon Cake</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Oh hey! Perhaps you know how much I love making cakes. And I have decided to make one big cake for my fellow friends, including you! I'd like to be special for Moon Festival and I'm sure you'll love it. I'll only need some flour, some moon sand and some milk. I've got the rest!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Visit the farmers and I'm sure you can get from them what we need.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Here you go, a delicious piece of my new cake and also some coins for your BIG help! Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Music Festival Party Plot -->
	<QUEST ID="Q201707a">
	    <NAME>Getting Sound Samples</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey hey hey! Lily's helping out Pandas with making music during this Music Festival! For sure, she's composing the BEST music out there. Of course, she needed help with building all this and now she needs help with assisting Pandas like you throughout their Superstar Journey.
The first thing we'll start with is getting sound samples for composing your biggest hit. Use the Composer at Harvest Grove with at least 3 other Pandas!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
In order to start your Superstar Journey, you'll have to compose some samples at Harvest Grove using the Composer.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done! Check back later for the next part of your journey. Now, take this prize, you'll also need a suitable outfit when jamming later!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201707b">
	    <NAME>Feeling the Rhythm</NAME>
	    <START>NPC001</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Yeah there! Music Festival is in its full swing and I'm here to help you feel the rhythm! Your task is simple - find all the 10 Xs, go on them, dance on them and click on them!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Some of the Xs include dance floor locations. After you dance on all the 10 Xs, come back here, dance and click on the X.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Good moves! Well done mate, here's your prize. You're learning quickly!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201707c">
	    <NAME>Wild Dances</NAME>
	    <START>NPC004</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC004</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Yo! I may be selling fishing poles and other stuff here all day, but this doesn't mean that I don't like to dance! After William McWiggles helped you practice your dance moves, it's time to dance together with other Pandas!
Find the place that I'll give you as a riddle and dance there with at least 4 other Pandas. And... here's the riddle: "Shake it off in front of a microphone, where folklore and modern world with orange color get together."
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
You gotta dance with at least 4 other Pandas, while shaking it off in front of a microphone, where folklore and modern world with orange color get together.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
That was amazing! You really can dance with others! You can ask me whenever to join you in a band.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201707d">
	    <NAME>Visiting a Performance</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there Panda pal! My friend Lily is performing in Purple Door and I recommend you to check her performance out! It's stunning, it's impressive! I also heard you're on your Superstar Journey. Go and see her, this will help you out a lot, learning from the professional! Watch it until the end and make sure to get her autograph by clicking on her!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Lily performs My Heart Will Go On. Isn't this song truly amazing?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
You saw her performance? Great! I hope you were also impressed by it, My Heart Will Go On is just a beautiful song! Here's something for you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201707e">
	    <NAME>Watching a Concert With Friends</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello! If you've seen Lily's performance, then you'd probably love this task - bring some friends to her live concert! If not, what's better than attending a brand new performance with 5 other Pandas? Check out her live concert every 15 minutes in Purple Door! Make sure to wait until the end!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Check out Lily's performance in Purple Door with 5 friends and watch it until the end!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
I'm pretty sure you'd love to visit it again and again, am I right? Here's something to remind you of today!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201707f">
	    <NAME>Collecting Final Ideas</NAME>
	    <START>NPC007</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC007</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! It's time for the last step before you're ready to become a superstar. This one is easy - go around Pandanda and collect five sound recordings from the music that's playing in these rooms. You'll use them later as resources for ideas in order to prepare a set of songs!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Your task is simple - just collect 5 sound recordings from a few places in Pandanda and then you'll be ready to prepare your set of songs and become a superstar!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done! Now, you can start preparing your songs. Come back later and get ready to go BIG! I'm giving you this shirt as a symbol of the happiness you're going to feel in the end of your Superstar Journey.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201707g">
	    <NAME>Becoming a Superstar</NAME>
	    <START>NPC012</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC012</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day my fellow pianist! Seems like visiting The Den and playing the piano has helped out. It's your big day and it's time to shine - just like Lily! Go to West Market Street and enter the Concert Hall next to Purple Door. There, click Now Playing and choose a song to perform. Go to the scene and start performing in front of at least 5 pandas! Perform the song until its end!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Enter the Concert Hall in West Market Street next to Purple Door and become a superstar on the scene!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
You're amazing! Phenomenal performance! Here's your Star Tee and remember - you're now a superstar and you have completed the Superstar Journey!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Panda Gold Quest -->
	<QUEST ID="Q201803">
	    <NAME>Golden Rumors</NAME>
	    <START>NPC0121</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC0121</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC0121</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there! Today, I've got a special secret for you to discover. mPandanda Land has always been full of treasures, but recently, Pandas have started discovering golden treasures. Try finding some in Pawthorne Forest and fishing some from Fishing Hole and Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Let's see if the old rumor is true: are there treasure chests to find in Pawthorne Forest and fish some from Fishing Hole and Coconut Beach.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done! Seems like it's all true: we can dig gold. Wondering what you can buy with it? Lily has the newest stuff on board. Check out if she can offer you something for the Panda Gold you can get from these chests.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Football Festival 2018 -->
	<QUEST ID="Q1806a">
	    <NAME>Flat Footballs</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Good day! Have you noticed flat footballs appearing around mPandanda recently? Seems like they just fall flat on the ground after Pandas kick them too hard. Can you find 5 of them appearing in other locations randomly and then find a tube of glue somewhere indoors so that I can fix them?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Flat footballs randomly appearing around definitely makes the landscape of our land worse.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks for bringing me those! I'll make sure to fix them as soon as possible, we're on a shortage with footballs.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1806b">
	    <NAME>Cutting the Grass</NAME>
	    <START>NPC005</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC005</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! As you probably know, I'm the green thumb of the land. So, I've noticed some grass being too tall in Bear Hollow, West Market Street and East Market Street. We need to make sure it's all cut, so could you look around carefully and cut it? 
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
We can't play football on a stadium with a grass that's way too grown, right?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
I'm sure that all the football players are thankful for your good deed!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1806c">
	    <NAME>Face Paint</NAME>
	    <START>NPC007</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC007</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
OMG, I'm a huge fan of face paints especially when it comes to football! That's sick dude! Can you go around and ask our fellas with the blue exclamations for some face paint of their color?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
What's your favorite face paint? I'll be putting on some green for the match tonight.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Sick colors! Let's go around and give some buckets away.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1806d">
	    <NAME>Match Invitations</NAME>
	    <START>NPC001</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there buddy! I'm a huge fan of football, or if you want, soccer, so I'm the one responsible to invite everybody to the match tonight. Can you give an invitation to every Panda with a blue exclamation mark?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
The best teams are playing at the match tonight - nobody should miss it!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks for the help! It's definitely going to be an amazing match.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1806e">
	    <NAME>Cleaning After the Match</NAME>
	    <START>NPC006</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC006</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello! Last night there was a match at the Stadium and seems like the fans threw trash away, not in the bins, but all around. Could you help me out with cleaning up? Also, there's some old newspapers in Bear Hollow and West Market Street to be thrown away.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
People can't play football when it looks like a dump all around. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks for helping me out with cleaning up! People will surely enjoy the match tonight again, make sure to raise awareness and tell everyone not to throw their trash around!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Sailors Festival -->
	
	<QUEST ID="Q201807a">
	    <NAME>The Beginning is Always Hard</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Arr harr! Aye! Pierre has told me you're up to your Pirate Journey. Wherever the wind blows gently, wherever the sun burns you nicely, wherever it sounds calming, wherever it's bright blue - that's the first place to go. Wherever this paradise is small and remote, that's the second place to go.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Hope you'll figure out my riddle! Wherever the wind blows gently, wherever the sun burns you nicely, wherever it sounds calming, wherever it's bright blue - that's the first place to go. Wherever this paradise is small and remote, that's the second place to go.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Aye! You've found the first map piece. Where to next, you'll find in the task to follow.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201807b">
	    <NAME>Bumpy, Jumpy, Wild</NAME>
	    <START>NPC009</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC009</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day me matey! It's time for your second task from your Pirate Journey. You'd ask, what is it? Bumpy, jumpy, that's where one goes. Not bumpy, not jumpy, wild, that's where the other one goes.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
That riddle is an easy one, I'm sure you'll figure it out!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done matey! Here's a prize for you and make sure to keep going on your Pirate Journey!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201807c">
	    <NAME>Where Any Other Panda Goes</NAME>
	    <START>NPC010</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC010</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Arr harr fella! Are you ready for a yet another prizelicious and delicious and adventurous part of your Pirate Jorney? Let's do this! Do you know where any other Panda goes? Do you know where cucumbers go? And do you really know where the fish goes?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Knowing mPandanda Land is very useful in this part of your Journey. Think beyond the borders!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Ayy, a very nice one, matey! Here's this fantasticious prize for you - don't give up, there's more to come!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201807d">
	    <NAME>Row Row Your Boat</NAME>
	    <START>NPC042</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC042</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC042</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day matey! Do ye think it's time to get into thay boat? Row, row, row your boat, gently down the stream! Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily, life is but a dream. And what about the mist in the sea, or more or less, on the land, arr?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Rowing your boat is an important skill of sailors, har har!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Har har! That ye be right! There be some prizes for ye. Don't forget to check out Row Your Boat game!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201807e">
	    <NAME>The Fish Goes Glub Glub</NAME>
	    <START>NPC004</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC004</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Ay, 'ello! Have you heard some interesting sounds, something in the water goes glub glub! You are asking where, that's near the starfish! And on the other end, we've got to harvest a map piece. So could you just check out what's going on with the glub-glubs and find the other map piece?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
That's a really mixed task, I know. But it's just some stuff to do if you're bored.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done on solving the riddle! Come back later in Bear Hollow, you're near the end of your Pirate Journey! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201807f">
	    <NAME>The Cow Goes Moo</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Are you ready for the last Pirate Journey task? Here we go! The first map piece is wherever the cow goes moo and the second one is near a cage.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
This, being the last task, is an easy one.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Oh my, I've just been told that there's one more task left of your journey. Well, here's a prize for finding (almost) the last two pieces!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q201807g">
	    <NAME>The End of the Pirate Journey</NAME>
	    <START>NPC042</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC042</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC042</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Arr harr, my fellow pirate! This ye be the final task of ye Pirate Journey! Are you ready to find the pirate booty? That ye be a hard task, har har! As the old pirate journal says, the treasure ye be in a land far, far away. Arr!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Where thar far away land ye be?
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
You have found the treasure!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Candy Festival -->
	<QUEST ID="Q1901a">
	    <NAME>Season's Greetings</NAME>
	    <START>NPC001</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there! Ice cream has been on low demand recently. With Candy Festival starting, it's just become a mess and now people are looking for candy. So, I decided to offer my clients some new special seasonal ice cream flavors. Will you help me and bring me 4 Peanut Butter Bars, 1 Sugar Beet and a Quart of Cream?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Alright, this seasonal candy will be a hit for sure.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thanks for bringing me those! Now let's melt the peanut butter candy bar and make it into a special Candy Festival ice cream!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1901b">
	    <NAME>Sugar and... Sugar?</NAME>
	    <START>NPC002</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC002</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
SUGAR SUGAR SUGAR! Oh, how much I love sugar! Awww man, I'm out of candy. I really need some. I know it's extremely bad for my health, but I promise, this will be my last candy intake for this festival. Will you find me some extra candy?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I really enjoy eating sweet stuff but I definitely should stop doing so.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Okay, I'll share this with you, I get it. I promised it was my last one. Here's some coins to thank you as well. HA! I GOT YOU! NEVER STOPPING! CANDY IS LOVE, CANDY IS LIFE! *runs away*
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1901c">
	    <NAME>Chocolate Supplies</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC001</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day, candy fan! As you probably know, Jack in The Orchard is trading some exclusive mPandanda Candy Bars for special amount of pieces of sweets collected. Pandas are so hyped that he needs large quantities of that mPandanda specialty. I'm going to look around for some chocolate, could you as well?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
As you have probably guessed, chocolate is the main ingredient of the mPD Candy Bar.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
That's really sweet of you, Lily and I have also collected a few more chocolates. I'll now use my special machine to make some of those, following the special recipe. Special ingredient? Panda love.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1901d">
	    <NAME>Lemon Candy</NAME>
	    <START>NPC010</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC010</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! Candy Festival is in its full swing and we've got loads of candy in. I really want to join in the huge sale with a special sour and sweet candy: lemon candy. Let's collect some fresh ingredients from The Orchard together: 2 Large Sugar Beets, 2 Medium Sugar Beets and 5 Lemons.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Many Pandas enjoy the sour and sweet taste, I hope they'll like my special candy flavor as well.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you! Now let's get this special candy made.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1901e">
	    <NAME>Eating Healthy</NAME>
	    <START>NPC024</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC024</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Okay, what's this euphoria? I bet it's due to that sugar overload. Really, Pandas need to stop eating that much candy. I've figured out the best way to promote healthy eating: we'll promote fruits and vegetables as candy. Let's say peaches and apples will be the sweet ones, whereas the tomatoes will be the sour ones. Of course, sugar-free.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
We should act now or Pandas won't stop indulging with that much candy, that's totally wrong.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you so much for supporting my idea! Now it's time to promote it around. Are you in?
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1901f">
	    <NAME>Hot Sweet Cucumbers</NAME>
	    <START>NPC014</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC014</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Thanks for stopping by, I've got to tell you something. Well, I'm completely supporting Maggie: this candy euphoria is not my cup of tea at all. However, my taste is a little bit odd, so I just can't go completely healthy. So let's see, I enjoy cucumbers, chili peppers and the sweet tase of sugar. So, I suppose I'll need a Sugar Beet, several Cucumbers, a few Chili Peppers and a Quart of Cream - that's to use as a base for the mix. Sounds weird, but I hope it'll work out well.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
This mix is weird indeed. But it's worth it to try.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you, now I gonna mix it, let's see what happens. Stop by later in order to get some feedback if you want!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Dragon Festival -->
	<QUEST ID="Q1904a">
	    <NAME>Festival Preparations</NAME>
	    <START>NPC007</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC007</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there! Dragon Festival has just started but it isn't really ready, there's some more stuff to be done. We need to blow up some balloons with helium and make final constructions with wood. Will you find 2 Helium Tanks that may be lost around the 'stars' or near a sweet water coast, as well as 4 pieces of Fresh Cut Wood from Pawthorne Forest?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
The final constructions won't take long, we will have everything set up in no time, especially with your help.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you so much for the help, now we can finish the Festival in full speed! Your daily prize is a Light Blue Pet Cap!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904b">
	    <NAME>Dragon Beds</NAME>
	    <START>NPC009</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC009</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day, fella! Dragon Festival is going great, isn't it? I really want to help Izzy so I've decided to make some little cute pet dragon beds. I'll need some materials, though: 4 pieces of Fresh Cut Wood from the Forest, paint from the famous Pandas that are willing to give out some for free and a Tube of Glue, hidden somewhere indoors.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
I have a really neat concept for them and I'll greatly appreciate it if you help me with the materials.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Now I get my concept done, thank you! Your daily prize is a Blue Bed!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904c">
	    <NAME>Pet Mats</NAME>
	    <START>NPC01337</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC01337</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC01337</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
It's the pets season and I thought that it'd be a good idea to knit some mats. I'm out of spools of thread and paint, but I'm sure you can find some by asking some of the famous Pandas around.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Those are going to look really cute, can't wait!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you so much for helping me out with my cute mats! Your daily prize is an Orange Pet Mat!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904d">
	    <NAME>Finding Food</NAME>
	    <START>NPC012</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC012</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey! There has been a high demand in the field of pet adoption recently and food is insufficient. Will you help me find 4 lost Bags of Pet Food?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Those pets are really hungry. Better feed them soon!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Yay, all the pets are now happy! Your daily prize is a Pets Tee!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904e">
	    <NAME>Light It Up</NAME>
	    <START>NPC5524</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC5524</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC5524</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
It's so nice to see you! Dragon Festival needs some lights put here and there but for that we need some strings and wiring. I'll do the wiring, but I'll need you to see if any Pandas can give you lightbulbs as well as some thicker thread in order to fix some of the bulbs properly. For the wiring, we'll need a few pieces of iron string that can be found in West Market Street, I suppose.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Scotch tape for fixing the bulbs is way old-fashioned. Thread for the win!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Thank you for helping me out, now Jim and I are going to do the wiring. Let's light it up! Your daily prize is a Pet Lamp!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904f">
	    <NAME>Entertaining Pets</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
What a nice day to have fun with pets! Today, I will be doing some clown tricks with them but I need a special outfit. Can you find by any chance any Panda that has a spare Clown Wig and a Red Nose?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Clowns are not necessarily scary. I'll be a funny clown!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Sweet, now it's my time to shine: I'll show that clowns are not necessarily scary, they can be funny and cute! Your daily prize is Ice Pet Wings!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904g">
	    <NAME>Lost Dragons</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hey there! With the beginning of Dragon Festival many Pandas have tamed dragons. However, many have escaped and now are roaming around mPandanda! Will you find all of them?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Those dragons could have flown anywhere. Better find them soon!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done, not many can tame 10 dragons altogether! Your daily prize is A Firebreather Mask!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904h">
	    <NAME>Grassy Lime</NAME>
	    <START>NPC012</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC012</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
G'day fellow Panda Pal! Today's task is easy: we need some grass clippings in order to color some pets. Oh, and some water resistant glue to glue the clippings to them.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
Painting the pets in green, what an idea!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Good job fella! We've got a new pet color - a Lime Pet! Your daily prize is a Lime Pet, that's now waiting for you in your treehouse!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q1904i">
	    <NAME>Taming a Dragon</NAME>
	    <START>NPC018</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC018</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
Hello there and welcome back. It's your very important day. A few Pandas have seen a new dragon going around mPandanda wildly. You need to help me with taming it. It can be literally anywhere - indoors and outdoors.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>
This dragon has to be tamed quickly.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>
Well done and congratulations on taming this dragon! The codename for your daily prize is: RAINBOWDRAGON.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
</QUESTS>